{
    "2021": {
        "november": {
            "language": {
                "afrikaans": [
                    {
                        "id": 1,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-FAL-P1-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/AfrIkaans-FAL-P1-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 2,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-FAL-P2-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-FAL-P2-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 3,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-FAL-P3-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-FAL-P3-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 4,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-HL-P1-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-HL-P1-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 5,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-HL-P2-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-HL-P2-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 6,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-HL-P3-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-HL-P3-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 7,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Secondary Additional Language P2 (Eastern Cape)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P2-Nov-2021-Eastern-Cape.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Eastern-Cape.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 8,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Secondary Additional Language P2 (Free State)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P2-Nov-2021-Free-State.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Free-State.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 9,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Secondary Additional Language P2 (Gauteng)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P2-Nov-2021-Gauteng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Gauteng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 10,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Secondary Additional Language P2 (KwaZulu-Natal)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P2-Nov-2021-KwaZulu-Natal.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P2-Nov-2021-MG-KwaZulu-Natal.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 11,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Secondary Additional Language P2 (Limpopo)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P2-Nov-2021-Limpopo.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Limpopo-2.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 12,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Secondary Additional Language P2 (Mpumalanga)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P2-Nov-2021-Mpumalanga.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Mpumalanga.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 13,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Secondary Additional Language P2 (North West)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P2-Nov-2021-North-West.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P2-Nov-2021-MG-North-West.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 14,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Secondary Additional Language P2 (Northern Cape)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P2-Nov-2021-Northern-Cape.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 15,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Secondary Additional Language P2 (Western Cape)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P2-Nov-2021-Western-Cape.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Wes-Kaap.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 16,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Second Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P3-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P3-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "english": [
                    {
                        "id": 17,
                        "subject": "english",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-FAL-P1-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-FAL-P1-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 18,
                        "subject": "english",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-FAL-P2-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-FAL-P2-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 19,
                        "subject": "english",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-FAL-P3-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-FAL-P3-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 20,
                        "subject": "english",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-HL-P1-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-HL-P1-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 21,
                        "subject": "english",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-HL-P2-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-HL-P2-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 22,
                        "subject": "english",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-HL-P3-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-HL-P3-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "isindebele": [
                    {
                        "id": 23,
                        "subject": "isindebele",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiNdebele-FAL-P1-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiNdebele-FAL-P1-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 24,
                        "subject": "isindebele",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiNdebele-FAL-P2-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiNdebele-FAL-P2-Nov-2021-1.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 25,
                        "subject": "isindebele",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiNdebele-FAL-P3-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiNdebele-FAL-P3-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 26,
                        "subject": "isindebele",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiNdebele-HL-P1-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiNdebele-HL-P1-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 27,
                        "subject": "isindebele",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiNdebele-HL-P2-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiNdebele-HL-P2-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 28,
                        "subject": "isindebele",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiNdebele-HL-P3-Nov-2021-MG.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiNdebele-HL-P3-Nov-2021.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 29,
                        "subject": "isindebele",
                        "title": "Second Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiNdebele-SAL-P1-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiNdebele-SAL-P1-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 30,
                        "subject": "isindebele",
                        "title": "Second Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiNdebele-SAL-P2-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiNdebele-SAL-P2-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 31,
                        "subject": "isindebele",
                        "title": "Second Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiNdebele-SAL-P3-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiNdebele-SAL-P3-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "isixhosa": [
                    {
                        "id": 32,
                        "subject": "isixhosa",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiXhosa-FAL-P1-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiXhosa-FAL-P1-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 33,
                        "subject": "isixhosa",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiXhosa-FAL-P2-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiXhosa-FAL-P2-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 34,
                        "subject": "isixhosa",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiXhosa-FAL-P3-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiXhosa-FAL-P3-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 35,
                        "subject": "isixhosa",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiXhosa-HL-P1-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiXhosa-HL-P1-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 36,
                        "subject": "isixhosa",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiXhosa-HL-P2-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiXhosa-HL-P2-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 37,
                        "subject": "isixhosa",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiXhosa-HL-P3-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiXhosa-HL-P3-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 38,
                        "subject": "isixhosa",
                        "title": "Second Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiXhosa-SAL-P1-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiXhosa-SAL-P1-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 39,
                        "subject": "isixhosa",
                        "title": "Second Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiXhosa-SAL-P2-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiXhosa-SAL-P2-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 40,
                        "subject": "isixhosa",
                        "title": "Second Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiXhosa-SAL-P3-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiXhosa-SAL-P3-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "isizulu": [
                    {
                        "id": 41,
                        "subject": "isizulu",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiZulu-FAL-P1-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiZulu-FAL-P1-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 42,
                        "subject": "isizulu",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiZulu-FAL-P2-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiZulu-FAL-P2-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 43,
                        "subject": "isizulu",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiZulu-FAL-P3-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiZulu-FAL-P3-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 44,
                        "subject": "isizulu",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiZulu-HL-P1-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiZulu-HL-P1-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 45,
                        "subject": "isizulu",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiZulu-HL-P2-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiZulu-HL-P2-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 46,
                        "subject": "isizulu",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiZulu-HL-P3-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiZulu-HL-P3-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 47,
                        "subject": "isizulu",
                        "title": "Second Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiZulu-SAL-P1-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiZulu-SAL-P1-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 48,
                        "subject": "isizulu",
                        "title": "Second Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiZulu-SAL-P2-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiXhosa-SAL-P2-Nov-2021-MG-1.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 49,
                        "subject": "isizulu",
                        "title": "Second Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiZulu-SAL-P3-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiZulu-SAL-P3-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "sepedi": [
                    {
                        "id": 50,
                        "subject": "sepedi",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-FAL-P1-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-FAL-P1-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 51,
                        "subject": "sepedi",
                        "title": "Secondary Additional Language P2 (Gauteng)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-SAL-P2-Nov-2021-Gauteng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 52,
                        "subject": "sepedi",
                        "title": "Paper 2 Second Additional Language (Limpopo)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-SAL-P2-Nov-2021-Limpopo.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-SAL-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Limpopo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 53,
                        "subject": "sepedi",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-HL-P3-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-HL-P3-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 54,
                        "subject": "sepedi",
                        "title": "Second Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-SAL-P3-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-SAL-P3-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 55,
                        "subject": "sepedi",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-HL-P2-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-HL-P2-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 56,
                        "subject": "sepedi",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-HL-P1-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-HL-P1-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 57,
                        "subject": "sepedi",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-FAL-P3-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-FAL-P3-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 58,
                        "subject": "sepedi",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-FAL-P2-Nov-2021-1.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-FAL-P2-Nov-2021-MG-1.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "sesotho": [
                    {
                        "id": 59,
                        "subject": "sesotho",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sesotho-FAL-P1-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sesotho-FAL-P1-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 60,
                        "subject": "sesotho",
                        "title": "Second Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sesotho-SAL-P2-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sesotho-SAL-P2-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 61,
                        "subject": "sesotho",
                        "title": "Second Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sesotho-SAL-P1-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sesotho-SAL-P1-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 62,
                        "subject": "sesotho",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sesotho-HL-P3-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sesotho-HL-P3-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 63,
                        "subject": "sesotho",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sesotho-HL-P2-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sesotho-HL-P2-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 64,
                        "subject": "sesotho",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sesotho-HL-P1-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sesotho-HL-P1-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 65,
                        "subject": "sesotho",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sesotho-FAL-P3-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sesotho-FAL-P3-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 66,
                        "subject": "sesotho",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sesotho-FAL-P2-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sesotho-FAL-P2-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 67,
                        "subject": "sesotho",
                        "title": "Second Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sesotho-SAL-P3-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sesotho-SAL-P3-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "setswana": [
                    {
                        "id": 68,
                        "subject": "setswana",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-FAL-P1-Nov-2021-MG-1.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 69,
                        "subject": "setswana",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-FAL-P2-Nov-2021-MG-4.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 70,
                        "subject": "setswana",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-FAL-P3-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-FAL-P3-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 71,
                        "subject": "setswana",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-HL-P1-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-HL-P1-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 72,
                        "subject": "setswana",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-HL-P2-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-HL-P2-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 73,
                        "subject": "setswana",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-HL-P3-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-HL-P3-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "siswati": [
                    {
                        "id": 74,
                        "subject": "siswati",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-FAL-P1-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-FAL-P1-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 75,
                        "subject": "siswati",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-FAL-P2-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-FAL-P2-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 76,
                        "subject": "siswati",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-FAL-P3-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-FAL-P3-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 77,
                        "subject": "siswati",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-HL-P1-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-HL-P1-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 78,
                        "subject": "siswati",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-HL-P2-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-HL-P2-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 79,
                        "subject": "siswati",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-HL-P3-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-HL-P3-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "tshivenda": [
                    {
                        "id": 80,
                        "subject": "tshivenda",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-FAL-P1-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-FAL-P1-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 81,
                        "subject": "tshivenda",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-FAL-P2-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-FAL-P2-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 82,
                        "subject": "tshivenda",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-FAL-P3-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-FAL-P3-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 83,
                        "subject": "tshivenda",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-HL-P1-Nov-2021.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 84,
                        "subject": "tshivenda",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-HL-P2-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 85,
                        "subject": "tshivenda",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-HL-P3-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-HL-P3-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "xitsonga": [
                    {
                        "id": 86,
                        "subject": "xitsonga",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-FAL-P1-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-FAL-P1-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 87,
                        "subject": "xitsonga",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-FAL-P2-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-FAL-P2-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 88,
                        "subject": "xitsonga",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-FAL-P3-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-FAL-P3-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 89,
                        "subject": "xitsonga",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-HL-P1-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-HL-P1-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 90,
                        "subject": "xitsonga",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-HL-P2-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-HL-P2-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 91,
                        "subject": "xitsonga",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-HL-P3-Nov-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-HL-P3-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "sign-language": [
                    {
                        "id": 92,
                        "subject": "sign-language",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/SASL-HL-P1-Nov-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 93,
                        "subject": "sign-language",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {}
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 94,
                        "subject": "sign-language",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {}
                    }
                ]
            },
            "non-language": {
                "afrikaans": [
                    {
                        "id": 95,
                        "subject": "Accounting",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Accounting-P1-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Accounting-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 96,
                        "subject": "Accounting",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Accounting-P2-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Accounting-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 97,
                        "subject": "Agricultural Management Practices",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Management-Practices-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Management-Practices-Nov-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 98,
                        "subject": "Agricultural Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Sciences-P1-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Sciences-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 99,
                        "subject": "Agricultural Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Sciences-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Afr-1.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 100,
                        "subject": "Agricultural Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Technology-Nov-2020-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Technology-Nov-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 101,
                        "subject": "Business Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Business-Studies-P1-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Business-Studies-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 102,
                        "subject": "Business Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Business-Studies-P2-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 103,
                        "subject": "Civil Technology",
                        "title": "Woodworking Paper 1",
                        "papers": {}
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 104,
                        "subject": "Civil Technology",
                        "title": "Civil Services Paper 1",
                        "papers": {}
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 105,
                        "subject": "Civil Technology",
                        "title": "Construction Paper 1",
                        "papers": {}
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 106,
                        "subject": "Computer Application Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Computer-Application-Technology-P1-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Computer-Application-Technology-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 107,
                        "subject": "Computer Application Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Computer-Application-Technology-P2-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Computer-Application-Technology-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 108,
                        "subject": "Consumer Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Consumer-Studies-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Consumer-Studies-Nov-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 109,
                        "subject": "Dance studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Dance-Studies-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Dance-Studies-Nov-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 110,
                        "subject": "Design",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Design-P1-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Design-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 111,
                        "subject": "Design",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Design-P2-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 112,
                        "subject": "Dramatic Arts",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Dramatic-Arts-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Dramatic-Arts-Nov-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 113,
                        "subject": "Economics",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Economics-P1-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Economics-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 114,
                        "subject": "Economics",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Economics-P2-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Economics-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 115,
                        "subject": "Electrical Technology",
                        "title": "Digitals Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Electrical-Technology-Nov-2021-Digital-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Electrical-Technology-Nov-2021-Digital-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 116,
                        "subject": "Electrical Technology",
                        "title": "Electronics Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Electrical-Technology-Nov-2021-Electronics-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Electrical-Technology-Nov-2021-Electronics-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 117,
                        "subject": "Electrical Technology",
                        "title": "Power Systems Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Electrical-Technology-Nov-2021-Power-Systems-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Electrical-Technology-Nov-2021-Power-Systems-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 118,
                        "subject": "Engineering Graphic and Design",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Engineering-Graphics-Design-P1-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Engineering-Graphics-Design-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 119,
                        "subject": "Engineering Graphic and Design",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Engineering-Graphics-Design-P2-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Engineering-Graphics-Design-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 120,
                        "subject": "Geography",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Geography-P1-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Geography-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 121,
                        "subject": "Geography",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Geography-P2-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Geography-P2-Nov-2020-Memo-Afr-2.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 122,
                        "subject": "History",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/History-P1-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/History-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 123,
                        "subject": "History",
                        "title": "Paper 1 Addendum",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/History-P1-Nov-2021-Addendum-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 124,
                        "subject": "History",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/History-P2-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/History-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 125,
                        "subject": "History",
                        "title": "Paper 2 Addendum",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/History-P2-Nov-2021-Addendum-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 126,
                        "subject": "Hospitality Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Hospitality-Studies-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Hospitality-Studies-Nov-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 127,
                        "subject": "Information Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Information-Technology-P1-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Information-Technology-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 128,
                        "subject": "Information Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Information-Technology-P2-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Information-Technology-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 129,
                        "subject": "Life Orientation",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Life-Orientation-September-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Life-Orientation-September-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 130,
                        "subject": "Life Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Life-Sciences-P1-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Life-Sciences-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 131,
                        "subject": "Life Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Life-Sciences-P2-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Life-Sciences-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 132,
                        "subject": "Mathematical Literacy",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematical-Literacy-P1-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematical-Literacy-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 133,
                        "subject": "Mathematical Literacy",
                        "title": "Paper 1 Addendum",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematical-Literacy-P1-Nov-2021-Addendum-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 134,
                        "subject": "Mathematical Literacy",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematical-Literacy-P2-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematical-Literacy-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 135,
                        "subject": "Mathematical Literacy",
                        "title": "Paper 2 Addendum",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematical-Literacy-P2-Nov-2021-Addendum-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 136,
                        "subject": "Mathematics",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematics-P2-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematics-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 137,
                        "subject": "Mathematics",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematics-P1-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematics-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 138,
                        "subject": "Mechanical Technology",
                        "title": "Welding and Metalwork Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mechanical-Technology-Nov-2021-Welding-Metalwork-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mechanical-Technology-Nov-2021-Welding-Metalwork-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 139,
                        "subject": "Mechanical Technology",
                        "title": "Fitting and Machining Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mechanical-Technology-Nov-2021-Fitting-Machining-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mechanical-Technology-Nov-2021-Fitting-Machining-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 140,
                        "subject": "Mechanical Technology",
                        "title": "Automative Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mechanical-Technology-Nov-2021-Automotive-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mechanical-Technology-Nov-2021-Automotive-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 141,
                        "subject": "Music",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Music-P2-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Music-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 142,
                        "subject": "Music",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Music-P1-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Music-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 143,
                        "subject": "Physical Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Physical-Sciences-P2-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Physical-Sciences-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 144,
                        "subject": "Physical Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Physical-Sciences-P1-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Physical-Sciences-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 145,
                        "subject": "Religion Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Religion-Studies-P2-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Religion-Studies-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 146,
                        "subject": "Religion Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Religion-Studies-P1-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Religion-Studies-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 147,
                        "subject": "Technical Mathematics",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Mathematics-P2-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Mathematics-P2-Nov-2021-Answer-Book-Eng-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 148,
                        "subject": "Technical Mathematics",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Mathematics-P1-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Mathematics-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 149,
                        "subject": "Technical Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Sciences-P2-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Sciences-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Eng-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 150,
                        "subject": "Technical Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Sciences-P1-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Sciences-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Eng-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 151,
                        "subject": "Tourism",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tourism-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tourism-Nov-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 152,
                        "subject": "Visual Arts",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Visual-Arts-P2-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 153,
                        "subject": "Visual Arts",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Visual-Arts-P1-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Visual-Arts-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "english": [
                    {
                        "id": 154,
                        "subject": "Accounting",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Accounting-P1-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Accounting-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 155,
                        "subject": "Accounting",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Accounting-P2-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Accounting-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 156,
                        "subject": "Agricultural Management Practices",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Management-Practices-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Management-Practices-Nov-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 157,
                        "subject": "Agricultural Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Sciences-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 158,
                        "subject": "Agricultural Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Sciences-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 159,
                        "subject": "Agricultural Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Technology-Nov-2021-MG-Eng-2.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 160,
                        "subject": "Business Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Business-Studies-P2-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Business-Studies-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 161,
                        "subject": "Business Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {}
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 162,
                        "subject": "Civil Technology",
                        "title": "Civil Services Paper 1",
                        "papers": {}
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 163,
                        "subject": "Civil Technology",
                        "title": "Construction Paper 1",
                        "papers": {}
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 164,
                        "subject": "Civil Technology",
                        "title": "Woodworking Paper 1",
                        "papers": {}
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 165,
                        "subject": "Computer Application Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Computer-Application-Technology-P1-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Computer-Application-Technology-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 166,
                        "subject": "Computer Application Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Computer-Application-Technology-P2-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Computer-Application-Technology-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 167,
                        "subject": "Consumer Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Consumer-Studies-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Consumer-Studies-Nov-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 168,
                        "subject": "Dance studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Dance-Studies-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Dance-Studies-Nov-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 169,
                        "subject": "Design",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Design-P1-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Design-P1-Nov-2020-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 170,
                        "subject": "Design",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Design-P2-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 171,
                        "subject": "Dramatic Arts",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Dramatic-Arts-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Dramatic-Arts-Nov-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 172,
                        "subject": "Economics",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Economics-P1-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Economics-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 173,
                        "subject": "Economics",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Economics-P2-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Economics-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 174,
                        "subject": "Electrical Technology",
                        "title": "Digitals Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Electrical-Technology-Nov-2021-Digital-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Electrical-Technology-Nov-2021-Digital-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 175,
                        "subject": "Electrical Technology",
                        "title": "Electronics Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Electrical-Technology-Nov-2021-Electronics-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Electrical-Technology-Nov-2021-Electronics-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 176,
                        "subject": "Electrical Technology",
                        "title": "Power Systems Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Electrical-Technology-Nov-2021-Power-Systems-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Electrical-Technology-Nov-2021-Power-Systems-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 177,
                        "subject": "Engineering Graphic and Design",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Engineering-Graphics-Design-P1-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Engineering-Graphics-Design-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 178,
                        "subject": "Engineering Graphic and Design",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Engineering-Graphics-Design-P2-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Engineering-Graphics-Design-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 179,
                        "subject": "Geography",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Geography-P1-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Geography-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 180,
                        "subject": "Geography",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Geography-P2-Nov-2020-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Geography-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 181,
                        "subject": "History",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/History-P1-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/History-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 182,
                        "subject": "History",
                        "title": "Paper 1 Addendum",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/History-P1-Nov-2021-Addendum-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 183,
                        "subject": "History",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/History-P2-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/History-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 184,
                        "subject": "History",
                        "title": "Paper 2 Addendum",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/History-P2-Nov-2021-Addendum-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 185,
                        "subject": "Hospitality Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Hospitality-Studies-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Hospitality-Studies-Nov-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 186,
                        "subject": "Information Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Information-Technology-P1-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Information-Technology-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 187,
                        "subject": "Information Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Information-Technology-P2-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Information-Technology-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 188,
                        "subject": "Life Orientation",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Life-Orientation-September-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Life-Orientation-September-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 189,
                        "subject": "Life Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Life-Sciences-P1-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Life-Sciences-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 190,
                        "subject": "Life Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Life-Sciences-P2-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Life-Sciences-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 191,
                        "subject": "Mathematical Literacy",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematical-Literacy-P1-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematical-Literacy-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 192,
                        "subject": "Mathematical Literacy",
                        "title": "Paper 1 Addendum",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematical-Literacy-P1-Nov-2021-Addendum-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 193,
                        "subject": "Mathematical Literacy",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematical-Literacy-P2-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematical-Literacy-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 194,
                        "subject": "Mathematical Literacy",
                        "title": "Paper 2 Addendum",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematical-Literacy-P2-Nov-2021-Addendum-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 195,
                        "subject": "Mathematics",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematics-P2-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematics-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 196,
                        "subject": "Mathematics",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematics-P1-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematics-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 197,
                        "subject": "Marine Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Marine-Sciences-P1-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Marine-Sciences-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 198,
                        "subject": "Marine Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Marine-Sciences-P2-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Marine-Sciences-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 199,
                        "subject": "Mechanical Technology",
                        "title": "Welding and Metalwork Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mechanical-Technology-Nov-2021-Welding-Metalwork-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mechanical-Technology-Nov-2021-Welding-Metalwork-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 200,
                        "subject": "Mechanical Technology",
                        "title": "Fitting and Machining Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mechanical-Technology-Nov-2021-Fitting-Machining-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mechanical-Technology-Nov-2021-Fitting-Machining-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 201,
                        "subject": "Mechanical Technology",
                        "title": "Automative Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mechanical-Technology-Nov-2021-Automotive-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mechanical-Technology-Nov-2021-Automotive-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 202,
                        "subject": "Music",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Music-P2-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Music-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 203,
                        "subject": "Music",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Music-P1-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Music-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 204,
                        "subject": "Physical Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Physical-Sciences-P2-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Physical-Sciences-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 205,
                        "subject": "Physical Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Physical-Sciences-P1-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Physical-Sciences-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 206,
                        "subject": "Religion Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Religion-Studies-P2-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Religion-Studies-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 207,
                        "subject": "Religion Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Religion-Studies-P1-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Religion-Studies-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 208,
                        "subject": "Technical Mathematics",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Mathematics-P2-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Mathematics-P2-Nov-2021-Answer-Book-Eng-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 209,
                        "subject": "Technical Mathematics",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Mathematics-P1-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Mathematics-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 210,
                        "subject": "Technical Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Sciences-P2-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Sciences-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Eng-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 211,
                        "subject": "Technical Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Sciences-P1-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Sciences-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Eng-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 212,
                        "subject": "Tourism",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tourism-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tourism-Nov-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 213,
                        "subject": "Visual Arts",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Visual-Arts-P2-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 214,
                        "subject": "Visual Arts",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Visual-Arts-P1-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Visual-Arts-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ]
            }
        },
        "may-june": {
            "language": {
                "afrikaans": [
                    {
                        "id": 215,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-FAL-P1-May-June-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-FAL-P1-May-June-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 216,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-FAL-P2-May-June-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-FAL-P2-May-June-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 217,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-FAL-P3-May-June-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-FAL-P3-May-June-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 218,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-HL-P1-May-June-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-HL-P1-May-June-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 219,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-HL-P2-May-June-2021-1.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-HL-P2-May-June-2021-MG-2.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 220,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-HL-P3-May-June-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-HL-P3-May-June-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 221,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Secondary Additional Language P1 (Eastern Cape)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-May-June-2021-Eastern-Cape.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Eastern-Cape.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 222,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Secondary Additional Language P1 (Free State)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-May-June-2021-Free-State.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Free-State.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 223,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Secondary Additional Language P1 (Gauteng)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-May-June-2021-Gauteng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Gauteng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 224,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Secondary Additional Language P1 (KwaZulu-Natal)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-May-June-2021-KwaZulu-Natal.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-May-June-2021-MG-KwaZulu-Natal.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 225,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Secondary Additional Language P1 (Limpopo)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-May-June-2021-Limpopo.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Limpopo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 226,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Secondary Additional Language P1 (Mpumalanga)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-May-June-2021-Mpumalanga.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Mpumalanga.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 227,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Secondary Additional Language P1 (North West)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-May-June-2021-North-West.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-May-June-2021-MG-North-West.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 228,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Secondary Additional Language P1 (Northern Cape)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-May-June-2021-Northern-Cape.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Northern-Cape.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 229,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Secondary Additional Language P1 (Western Cape)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-May-June-2021-Western-Cape.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Western-Cape.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 230,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Second Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P2-May-June-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P2-May-June-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "english": [
                    {
                        "id": 231,
                        "subject": "english",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-FAL-P1-May-June-2021-1.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-FAL-P1-May-June-2021-MG-1.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 232,
                        "subject": "english",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-FAL-P2-May-June-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-FAL-P2-May-June-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 233,
                        "subject": "english",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-FAL-P3-May-June-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-FAL-P3-May-June-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 234,
                        "subject": "english",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-HL-P1-May-June-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-HL-P1-May-June-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 235,
                        "subject": "english",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-HL-P2-May-June-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-HL-P2-May-June-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 236,
                        "subject": "english",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-HL-P3-May-June-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-HL-P3-May-June-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "sepedi": [
                    {
                        "id": 237,
                        "subject": "sepedi",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-FAL-P1-May-June-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-FAL-P1-May-June-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 238,
                        "subject": "sepedi",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-FAL-P2-May-June-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-FAL-P2-May-June-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 239,
                        "subject": "sepedi",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-FAL-P3-May-June-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-FAL-P3-May-June-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 240,
                        "subject": "sepedi",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-HL-P1-May-June-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-HL-P1-May-June-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 241,
                        "subject": "sepedi",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-HL-P2-May-June-2021.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 242,
                        "subject": "sepedi",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-HL-P3-May-June-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-HL-P3-May-June-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "setswana": [
                    {
                        "id": 243,
                        "subject": "setswana",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-FAL-P1-May-June-2021-MG.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-FAL-P1-May-June-2021.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 244,
                        "subject": "setswana",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-FAL-P2-May-June-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-FAL-P2-May-June-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 245,
                        "subject": "setswana",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-FAL-P3-May-June-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-FAL-P3-May-June-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 246,
                        "subject": "setswana",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-HL-P1-May-June-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-HL-P1-May-June-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 247,
                        "subject": "setswana",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-HL-P2-May-June-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-HL-P2-May-June-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 248,
                        "subject": "setswana",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-HL-P3-May-June-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-HL-P3-May-June-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "siswati": [
                    {
                        "id": 249,
                        "subject": "siswati",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-FAL-P1-May-June-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-FAL-P1-May-June-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 250,
                        "subject": "siswati",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-FAL-P2-May-June-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-FAL-P2-May-June-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 251,
                        "subject": "siswati",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-FAL-P3-May-June-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-FAL-P3-May-June-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 252,
                        "subject": "siswati",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-HL-P1-May-June-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-HL-P1-May-June-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 253,
                        "subject": "siswati",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-HL-P2-May-June-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-HL-P2-May-June-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 254,
                        "subject": "siswati",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-HL-P3-May-June-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-HL-P3-May-June-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "tshivenda": [
                    {
                        "id": 255,
                        "subject": "tshivenda",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-FAL-P1-May-June-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-FAL-P1-May-June-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 256,
                        "subject": "tshivenda",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-FAL-P2-May-June-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-FAL-P2-May-June-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 257,
                        "subject": "tshivenda",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-FAL-P3-May-June-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-FAL-P3-May-June-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 258,
                        "subject": "tshivenda",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-HL-P1-May-June-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-HL-P1-May-June-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 259,
                        "subject": "tshivenda",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-HL-P2-May-June-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-HL-P2-May-June-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 260,
                        "subject": "tshivenda",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-HL-P3-May-June-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-HL-P3-May-June-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "xitsonga": [
                    {
                        "id": 261,
                        "subject": "xitsonga",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-FAL-P1-May-June-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-FAL-P1-May-June-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 262,
                        "subject": "xitsonga",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-FAL-P2-May-June-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-FAL-P2-May-June-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 263,
                        "subject": "xitsonga",
                        "title": "First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-FAL-P3-May-June-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-FAL-P3-May-June-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 264,
                        "subject": "xitsonga",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-HL-P1-May-June-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-HL-P1-May-June-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 265,
                        "subject": "xitsonga",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-HL-P2-May-June-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-HL-P2-May-June-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 266,
                        "subject": "xitsonga",
                        "title": "Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-HL-P3-May-June-2021.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-HL-P3-May-June-2021-MG.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ]
            },
            "non-language": {
                "afrikaans": [
                    {
                        "id": 267,
                        "subject": "Accounting",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Accounting-P1-May-June-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Accounting-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 268,
                        "subject": "Accounting",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Accounting-P2-May-June-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Accounting-P2-May-June-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 269,
                        "subject": "Agricultural Management Practices",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Management-Practices-May-June-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Management-Practices-May-June-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 270,
                        "subject": "Agricultural Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Sciences-P1-May-June-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Sciences-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 271,
                        "subject": "Agricultural Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Sciences-P2-May-June-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Sciences-P2-May-June-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 272,
                        "subject": "Agricultural Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Technology-May-June-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Technology-May-June-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 273,
                        "subject": "Business Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Business-Studies-P1-May-June-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Business-Studies-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 274,
                        "subject": "Business Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Business-Studies-P2-May-June-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Business-Studies-P2-May-June-2021-MG-Afr-1.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 275,
                        "subject": "Civil Technology",
                        "title": "Civil services Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Civil-Technology-May-June-2021-Civil-Services-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Civil-Technology-May-June-2021-Civil-Services-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 276,
                        "subject": "Civil Technology",
                        "title": "Woodworking Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Civil-Technology-May-June-2021-Woodworking-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Civil-Technology-May-June-2021-Woodworking-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 277,
                        "subject": "Civil Technology",
                        "title": "Construction Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Civil-Technology-May-June-2021-Construction-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Civil-Technology-May-June-2021-Construction-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 278,
                        "subject": "Computer Application Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Computer-Application-Technology-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 279,
                        "subject": "Computer Application Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Computer-Application-Technology-P2-May-June-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Computer-Application-Technology-P2-May-June-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 280,
                        "subject": "Consumer Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Consumer-Studies-May-June-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Consumer-Studies-May-June-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 281,
                        "subject": "Dance studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Dance-Studies-May-June-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Dance-Studies-May-June-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 282,
                        "subject": "Design",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Design-P1-May-June-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Design-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 283,
                        "subject": "Dramatic Arts",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Dramatic-Arts-May-June-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Dramatic-Arts-May-June-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 284,
                        "subject": "Economics",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Economics-P1-Nov-2020-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Economics-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 285,
                        "subject": "Economics",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Economics-P2-May-June-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 286,
                        "subject": "Electrical Technology",
                        "title": "Digitals Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Electrical-Technology-May-June-2021-Digital-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Electrical-Technology-May-June-2021-Digital-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 287,
                        "subject": "Electrical Technology",
                        "title": "Electronic Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Electrical-Technology-May-June-2021-Electronics-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Electrical-Technology-May-June-2021-Electronics-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 288,
                        "subject": "Electrical Technology",
                        "title": "Power systems Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Electrical-Technology-May-June-2021-Power-Systems-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Electrical-Technology-May-June-2021-Power-Systems-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 289,
                        "subject": "Engineering Graphic and Design",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Engineering-Graphics-Design-P1-May-June-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/EGD-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 290,
                        "subject": "Engineering Graphic and Design",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Engineering-Graphics-Design-P2-May-June-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/EGD-P2-May-June-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 291,
                        "subject": "Geography",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Geography-P1-May-June-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Geography-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 292,
                        "subject": "Geography",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Geography-P2-May-June-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Geography-P2-May-June-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 293,
                        "subject": "Geography",
                        "title": "Paper 1 Annexure",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Geography-P1-May-June-2021-Annexure-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 294,
                        "subject": "History",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/History-P1-May-June-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/History-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 295,
                        "subject": "History",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/History-P2-May-June-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/History-P2-May-June-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 296,
                        "subject": "History",
                        "title": "Paper 1 Addendum",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/History-P1-May-June-2021-Addendum-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 297,
                        "subject": "History",
                        "title": "Paper 2  Addendum",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/History-P2-May-June-2021-Addendum-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 298,
                        "subject": "Hospitality Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Hospitality-Studies-May-June-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Hospitality-Studies-May-June-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 299,
                        "subject": "Information Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Information-Technology-P1-May-June-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Information-Technology-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 300,
                        "subject": "Information Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Information-Technology-P2-May-June-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Information-Technology-P2-May-June-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 301,
                        "subject": "Life Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Life-Sciences-P1-May-June-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Life-Sciences-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 302,
                        "subject": "Life Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Life-Sciences-P2-May-June-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Life-Sciences-P2-May-June-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 303,
                        "subject": "Mathematical Literacy",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematical-Literacy-P1-May-June-2021-Afr-1.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematical-Literacy-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Afr-Eng-1.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 304,
                        "subject": "Mathematical Literacy",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematical-Literacy-P2-May-June-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematical-Literacy-P2-May-June-2021-MG-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 305,
                        "subject": "Mathematical Literacy",
                        "title": "Paper 1 Addendum",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematical-Literacy-P1-May-June-2021-Addendum-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 306,
                        "subject": "Mathematical Literacy",
                        "title": "Paper 2 Addendum",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematical-Literacy-P2-May-June-2021-Addendum-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 307,
                        "subject": "Mathematics",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematics-P1-May-June-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematics-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 308,
                        "subject": "Mathematics",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematics-P2-May-June-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematics-P2-May-June-2021-MG-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 309,
                        "subject": "Mechanical Technology",
                        "title": "Welding and Metalwork Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mechanical-Technology-May-June-2021-Welding-Metalwork-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mechanical-Technology-May-June-2021-Welding-Metalwork-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 310,
                        "subject": "Mechanical Technology",
                        "title": "Fitting and Machining Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mechanical-Technology-May-June-2021-Fitting-Machining-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mechanical-Technology-May-June-2021-Fitting-Machining-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 311,
                        "subject": "Mechanical Technology",
                        "title": "Automative Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mechanical-Technology-May-June-2021-Automotive-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mechanical-Technology-May-June-2021-Automotive-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 312,
                        "subject": "Music",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Music-P2-May-June-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Music-P2-May-June-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 313,
                        "subject": "Music",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Music-P1-May-June-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Music-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 314,
                        "subject": "Physical Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Physical-Sciences-P2-May-June-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Physical-Sciences-P2-May-June-2021-MG-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 315,
                        "subject": "Physical Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Physical-Sciences-P1-May-June-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Physical-Sciences-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 316,
                        "subject": "Religion Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Religion-Studies-P2-May-June-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Religion-Studies-P2-May-June-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 317,
                        "subject": "Religion Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Religion-Studies-P1-May-June-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Religion-Studies-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 318,
                        "subject": "Technical Mathematics",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Mathematics-P2-May-June-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Mathematics-P2-May-June-2021-MG-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 319,
                        "subject": "Technical Mathematics",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Mathematics-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Eng-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 320,
                        "subject": "Technical Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Sciences-P2-May-June-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Sciences-P2-May-June-2021-MG-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 321,
                        "subject": "Technical Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Sciences-P1-May-June-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Sciences-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 322,
                        "subject": "Tourism",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tourism-May-June-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tourism-May-June-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 323,
                        "subject": "Visual Arts",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Visual-Arts-P1-May-June-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Visual-Arts-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "english": [
                    {
                        "id": 324,
                        "subject": "Accounting",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Accounting-P1-May-June-2021-Eng-1.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Accounting-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Eng-1.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 325,
                        "subject": "Accounting",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Accounting-P2-May-June-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Accounting-P2-May-June-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 326,
                        "subject": "Agricultural Management Practices",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Management-Practices-May-June-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Management-Practices-May-June-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 327,
                        "subject": "Agricultural Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Sciences-P1-May-June-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Sciences-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 328,
                        "subject": "Agricultural Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Sciences-P2-May-June-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Sciences-P2-May-June-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 329,
                        "subject": "Agricultural Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Technology-May-June-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Technology-May-June-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 330,
                        "subject": "Business Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Business-Studies-P1-May-June-2021-Eng-1.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Business-Studies-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Eng-1.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 331,
                        "subject": "Business Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Business-Studies-P2-May-June-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Business-Studies-P2-May-June-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 332,
                        "subject": "Civil Technology",
                        "title": "Civil services Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Civil-Technology-May-June-2021-Civil-Services-Eng-1.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Civil-Technology-May-June-2021-Civil-Services-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 333,
                        "subject": "Civil Technology",
                        "title": "Woodworking Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Civil-Technology-May-June-2021-Woodworking-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 334,
                        "subject": "Civil Technology",
                        "title": "Construction Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Civil-Technology-May-June-2021-Construction-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Civil-Technology-May-June-2021-Construction-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 335,
                        "subject": "Computer Application Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Computer-Application-Technology-P1-May-June-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Computer-Application-Technology-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 336,
                        "subject": "Computer Application Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Computer-Application-Technology-P2-May-June-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Computer-Application-Technology-P2-May-June-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 337,
                        "subject": "Consumer Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Consumer-Studies-May-June-2021-Eng.pdf",
                        "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Consumer-Studies-May-June-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 338,
                        "subject": "Dance studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Dance-Studies-May-June-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 339,
                        "subject": "Design",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Design-P1-May-June-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Design-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 340,
                        "subject": "Dramatic Arts",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Dramatic-Arts-May-June-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Dramatic-Arts-May-June-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 341,
                        "subject": "Economics",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Economics-P1-May-June-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Economics-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 342,
                        "subject": "Economics",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Economics-P2-May-June-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Economics-P2-May-June-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 343,
                        "subject": "Electrical Technology",
                        "title": "Digitals Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Electrical-Technology-May-June-2021-Digital-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Electrical-Technology-May-June-2021-Digital-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 344,
                        "subject": "Electrical Technology",
                        "title": "Electronic Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Electrical-Technology-Nov-2020-Electronics-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Electrical-Technology-May-June-2021-Electronics-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 345,
                        "subject": "Electrical Technology",
                        "title": "Power systems Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Electrical-Technology-May-June-2021-Power-Systems-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Electrical-Technology-May-June-2021-Power-Systems-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 346,
                        "subject": "Engineering Graphic and Design",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Engineering-Graphics-Design-P1-May-June-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/EGD-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 347,
                        "subject": "Engineering Graphic and Design",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Engineering-Graphics-Design-P2-May-June-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/EGD-P2-May-June-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 348,
                        "subject": "Geography",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Geography-P1-May-June-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Geography-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 349,
                        "subject": "Geography",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Geography-P2-May-June-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Geography-P2-May-June-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 350,
                        "subject": "Geography",
                        "title": "Paper 1 Annexure",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Geography-P1-May-June-2021-Annexure-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 351,
                        "subject": "History",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/History-P1-May-June-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/History-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 352,
                        "subject": "History",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/History-P2-May-June-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/History-P2-May-June-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 353,
                        "subject": "History",
                        "title": "Paper 1 Addendum",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/History-P1-May-June-2021-Addendum-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 354,
                        "subject": "History",
                        "title": "Paper 2 Addendum",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/History-P2-May-June-2021-Addendum-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 355,
                        "subject": "Hospitality Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Hospitality-Studies-May-June-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Hospitality-Studies-May-June-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 356,
                        "subject": "Information Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Information-Technology-P1-May-June-2021-Eng-1.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Information-Technology-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Eng-1.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 357,
                        "subject": "Information Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Information-Technology-P2-May-June-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Information-Technology-P2-May-June-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 358,
                        "subject": "Life Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Life-Sciences-P1-May-June-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Life-Sciences-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 359,
                        "subject": "Life Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Life-Sciences-P2-May-June-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Life-Sciences-P2-May-June-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 360,
                        "subject": "Mathematical Literacy",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematical-Literacy-P1-May-June-2021-Eng-1.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematical-Literacy-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Afr-Eng-1.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 361,
                        "subject": "Mathematical Literacy",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematical-Literacy-P2-May-June-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematical-Literacy-P2-May-June-2021-MG-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 362,
                        "subject": "Mathematical Literacy",
                        "title": "Paper 1 Addendum",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematical-Literacy-P1-May-June-2021-Addendum-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 363,
                        "subject": "Mathematical Literacy",
                        "title": "Paper 2 Addendum",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematical-Literacy-P2-May-June-2021-Addendum-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 364,
                        "subject": "Mathematics",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematics-P1-May-June-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematics-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 365,
                        "subject": "Mathematics",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematics-P2-May-June-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematics-P2-May-June-2021-MG-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 366,
                        "subject": "Mechanical Technology",
                        "title": "Welding and Metalwork Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mechanical-Technology-May-June-2021-Welding-Metalwork-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mechanical-Technology-May-June-2021-Welding-Metalwork-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 367,
                        "subject": "Mechanical Technology",
                        "title": "Fitting and Machining Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mechanical-Technology-May-June-2021-Fitting-Machining-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mechanical-Technology-May-June-2021-Fitting-Machining-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 368,
                        "subject": "Mechanical Technology",
                        "title": "Automative Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mechanical-Technology-May-June-2021-Automotive-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mechanical-Technology-May-June-2021-Automotive-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 369,
                        "subject": "Music",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Music-P2-May-June-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Music-P2-May-June-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 370,
                        "subject": "Music",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Music-P1-May-June-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Music-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 371,
                        "subject": "Physical Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Physical-Sciences-P2-May-June-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Physical-Sciences-P2-May-June-2021-MG-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 372,
                        "subject": "Physical Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Physical-Sciences-P1-May-June-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Physical-Sciences-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 373,
                        "subject": "Religion Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Physical-Sciences-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Afr-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Religion-Studies-P2-May-June-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 374,
                        "subject": "Religion Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Religion-Studies-P1-May-June-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Religion-Studies-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 375,
                        "subject": "Technical Mathematics",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Mathematics-P2-May-June-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Mathematics-P2-May-June-2021-MG-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 376,
                        "subject": "Technical Mathematics",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Mathematics-P1-May-June-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Mathematics-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Eng-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 377,
                        "subject": "Technical Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Sciences-P2-May-June-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Sciences-P2-May-June-2021-MG-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 378,
                        "subject": "Technical Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Sciences-P1-May-June-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Sciences-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 379,
                        "subject": "Tourism",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tourism-May-June-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tourism-May-June-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 380,
                        "subject": "Visual Arts",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Visual-Arts-P1-May-June-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Visual-Arts-P1-May-June-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ]
            }
        }
    },
    "2020": {
        "november": {
            "language": {
                "afrikaans": [
                    {
                        "id": 381,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-FAL-P1-Nov-2020.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-FAL-P1-Nov-2020-Memo-1.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 382,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-FAL-P2-Nov-2020.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-FAL-P2-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 383,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-FAL-P3-Nov-2020.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-FAL-P3-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 384,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans Home Language 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-HL-P1-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 385,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans Home Language 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-HL-P2-Nov-2020.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-HL-P2-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 386,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans Home Language 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-HL-P3-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 387,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans Second Additional Language P1(Eastern Cape)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-Nov-2020-Eastern-Cape.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-Nov-2020-Memo-Eastern-Cape.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 388,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans Second Additional Language P1(Free State)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-Nov-2020-Free-State.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-Nov-2020-Memo-Free-State.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 389,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans Second Additional Language P1(Gauteng)",
                        "papers": {}
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 390,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans Second Additional Language P1(Kwazulu-Natal)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-Nov-2020-KwaZulu-Natal.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-Nov-2020-Memo-KwaZulu-Natal.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 391,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans Second Additional Language P1(Limpopo)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-Nov-2020-Limpopo.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-Nov-2020-Memo-Limpopo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 392,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans Second Additional Language P1(North West)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-Nov-2020-North-West.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-Nov-2020-Memo-North-West.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 393,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans Second Additional Language P1(Northern Cape)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-Nov-2020-Northern-Cape.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 394,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans Second Additional Language P1(Western Cape)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-Nov-2020-Western-Cape.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-Nov-2020-Memo-Western-Cape.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 395,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans Second Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P2-Nov-2020.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P2-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "english": [
                    {
                        "id": 396,
                        "subject": "english",
                        "title": "English First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-FAL-P1-Nov-2020.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-FAL-P1-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 397,
                        "subject": "english",
                        "title": "English First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-FAL-P2-Nov-2020.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-FAL-P2-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 398,
                        "subject": "english",
                        "title": "English First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-FAL-P3-Nov-2020.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-FAL-P3-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 399,
                        "subject": "english",
                        "title": "English Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-HL-P1-Nov-2020.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-HL-P1-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 400,
                        "subject": "english",
                        "title": "English Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-HL-P2-Nov-2020.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-HL-P2-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 401,
                        "subject": "english",
                        "title": "English Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-HL-P3-Nov-2020.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-HL-P3-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "sepedi": [
                    {
                        "id": 402,
                        "subject": "sepedi",
                        "title": "Sepedi First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-FAL-P1-Nov-2020.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-FAL-P1-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 403,
                        "subject": "sepedi",
                        "title": "Sepedi First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-FAL-P2-Nov-2020.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-FAL-P2-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 404,
                        "subject": "sepedi",
                        "title": "Sepedi First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-FAL-P3-Nov-2020.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-FAL-P3-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 405,
                        "subject": "sepedi",
                        "title": "Sepedi Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-HL-P1-Nov-2020.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-HL-P1-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 406,
                        "subject": "sepedi",
                        "title": "Sepedi Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-HL-P2-Nov-2020.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-HL-P2-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 407,
                        "subject": "sepedi",
                        "title": "Sepedi Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-HL-P3-Nov-2020.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-HL-P3-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 408,
                        "subject": "sepedi",
                        "title": "Sepedi P1 SAL(Limpopo)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-SAL-P1-Nov-2020-Limpopo.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-SAL-P1-Nov-2020-Memo-Limpopo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 409,
                        "subject": "sepedi",
                        "title": "Sepedi Second Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-SAL-P2-Nov-2020.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-SAL-P2-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "setswana": [
                    {
                        "id": 410,
                        "subject": "setswana",
                        "title": "Setswana First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-FAL-P1-Nov-2020.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-FAL-P1-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 411,
                        "subject": "setswana",
                        "title": "Setswana First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-FAL-P2-Nov-2020.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-FAL-P2-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 412,
                        "subject": "setswana",
                        "title": "Setswana First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-FAL-P3-Nov-2020.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-FAL-P3-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 413,
                        "subject": "setswana",
                        "title": "Setswana Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-HL-P1-Nov-2020.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-HL-P1-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 414,
                        "subject": "setswana",
                        "title": "Setswana Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-HL-P2-Nov-2020.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-HL-P2-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 415,
                        "subject": "setswana",
                        "title": "Setswana Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-HL-P3-Nov-2020.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-HL-P3-Nov-2020.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "siswati": [
                    {
                        "id": 416,
                        "subject": "siswati",
                        "title": "Siswati First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-FAL-P1-Nov-2020-1.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-FAL-P1-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 417,
                        "subject": "siswati",
                        "title": "Siswati First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-FAL-P2-Nov-2020.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-FAL-P2-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 418,
                        "subject": "siswati",
                        "title": "Siswati First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-FAL-P3-Nov-2020.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-FAL-P3-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 419,
                        "subject": "siswati",
                        "title": "Siswati Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-HL-P1-Nov-2020.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-HL-P1-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 420,
                        "subject": "siswati",
                        "title": "Siswati Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-HL-P2-Nov-2020.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-HL-P2-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 421,
                        "subject": "siswati",
                        "title": "Siswati Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-HL-P3-Nov-2020.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-HL-P3-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "tshivenda": [
                    {
                        "id": 422,
                        "subject": "tshivenda",
                        "title": "Tshivenda First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-FAL-P1-Nov-2020.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-FAL-P1-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 423,
                        "subject": "tshivenda",
                        "title": "Tshivenda First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-FAL-P2-Nov-2020.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-FAL-P2-Nov-2020-Memo-1.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 424,
                        "subject": "tshivenda",
                        "title": "Tshivenda First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-FAL-P3-Nov-2020.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-FAL-P3-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 425,
                        "subject": "tshivenda",
                        "title": "Tshivenda Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-HL-P1-Nov-2020.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-HL-P1-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 426,
                        "subject": "tshivenda",
                        "title": "Tshivenda Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-HL-P2-Nov-2020.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-HL-P2-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 427,
                        "subject": "tshivenda",
                        "title": "Tshivenda Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-HL-P3-Nov-2020.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-HL-P3-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "xitsonga": [
                    {
                        "id": 428,
                        "subject": "xitsonga",
                        "title": "Xitsonga First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-FAL-P1-Nov-2020.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-FAL-P1-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 429,
                        "subject": "xitsonga",
                        "title": "Xitsonga First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-FAL-P2-Nov-2020.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-FAL-P2-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 430,
                        "subject": "xitsonga",
                        "title": "Xitsonga First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-FAL-P3-Nov-2020.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-FAL-P3-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 431,
                        "subject": "xitsonga",
                        "title": "Xitsonga Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-HL-P1-Nov-2020.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-HL-P1-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 432,
                        "subject": "xitsonga",
                        "title": "Xitsonga Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-HL-P2-Nov-2020.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-HL-P2-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 433,
                        "subject": "xitsonga",
                        "title": "Xitsonga Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-HL-P3-Nov-2020.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-HL-P3-Nov-2020-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "sign-language": [
                    {
                        "id": 434,
                        "subject": "south african sign language",
                        "title": "SASL Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {}
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 435,
                        "subject": "south african sign language",
                        "title": "SASL Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {}
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 436,
                        "subject": "south african sign language",
                        "title": "SASL Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {}
                    }
                ]
            },
            "non-language": {
                "afrikaans": [
                    {
                        "id": 437,
                        "subject": "Accounting",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Accounting-P1-NSC-Nov-2020-Afr-2.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Accounting-P1-Nov-2020-Memo-Afr-2.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 438,
                        "subject": "Accounting",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Accounting-P2-NSC-Nov-2020-Afr-2-1.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Accounting-P2-Nov-2020-Memo-Afr-2-1.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 439,
                        "subject": "Accounting (Senior Certificate)",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Accounting-SC-Nov-2020-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Accounting-Nov-2020-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 440,
                        "subject": "Agricultural Management Practices",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Management-Practices-Nov-2020-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Management-Practices-Nov-2020-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 441,
                        "subject": "Agricultural Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Sciences-P1-Nov-2020-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Sciences-P1-Nov-2020-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 442,
                        "subject": "Agricultural Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Sciences-P2-Nov-2020-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Sciences-P2-Nov-2020-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 443,
                        "subject": "Agricultural Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Technology-Nov-2020-Afr-1.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Technology-Nov-2020-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 444,
                        "subject": "Business Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Business-Studies-P1-NSC-Nov-2020-Afr-1.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 445,
                        "subject": "Business Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Business-Studies-P2-NSC-Nov-2020-Afr-2.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 446,
                        "subject": "Business Studies(Senior Certificate)",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Business-Studies-SC-Nov-2020-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Business-Studies-Nov-2020-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 447,
                        "subject": "Civil Technology",
                        "title": "Civil Services Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Civil-Technology-Nov-2020-Civil-Services-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Civil-Technology-Nov-2020-Civil-Services-Memo-Afr-1.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 448,
                        "subject": "Civil Technology",
                        "title": "Woodworking Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Civil-Technology-Nov-2020-Woodworking-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Civil-Technology-Nov-2020-Woodworking-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 449,
                        "subject": "Civil Technology",
                        "title": "Construction Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Civil-Technology-Nov-2020-Construction-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Civil-Technology-Nov-2020-Construction-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 450,
                        "subject": "Computer Application Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Computer-Application-Technology-P1-Nov-2020-Afr-1.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Computer-Application-Technology-P1-Nov-2020-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 451,
                        "subject": "Computer Application Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Computer-Application-Technology-P2-Nov-2020-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Computer-Application-Technology-P2-Nov-2020-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 452,
                        "subject": "Consumer Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Consumer-Studies-Nov-2020-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Consumer-Studies-Nov-2020-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 453,
                        "subject": "Dance Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Dance-Studies-Nov-2020-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Dance-Studies-Nov-2020-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 454,
                        "subject": "Design",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Design-P1-Nov-2020-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Design-P1-Nov-2020-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 455,
                        "subject": "Design",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Design-P2-Nov-2020-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 456,
                        "subject": "Dramatic Arts",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Dramatic-Arts-Nov-2020-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Dramatic-Arts-Nov-2020-Afr-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 457,
                        "subject": "Economics",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Economics-P1-Nov-2020-Afr-1.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Economics-P1-Nov-2020-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 458,
                        "subject": "Economics",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Economics-P2-Nov-2020-Afr-1.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Economics-P2-Nov-2020-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 459,
                        "subject": "Electrical Technology",
                        "title": "Digitals Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Electrical-Technology-Nov-2020-Digital-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Electrical-Technology-Nov-2020-Digital-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 460,
                        "subject": "Electrical Technology",
                        "title": "Electronic Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Electrical-Technology-Nov-2020-Electronics-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Electrical-Technology-Nov-2020-Electronics-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 461,
                        "subject": "Electrical Technology",
                        "title": "Power Systems Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Electrical-Technology-Nov-2020-Power-Systems-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Electrical-Technology-Nov-2020-Power-Systems-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 462,
                        "subject": "Engineering Graphic and Design",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Engineering-Graphics-Design-P1-Nov-2020-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/EGD-P1-Nov-2020-Afr-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 463,
                        "subject": "Engineering Graphic and Design",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Engineering-Graphics-Design-P2-Nov-2020-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/EGD-P2-Nov-2020-Afr-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 464,
                        "subject": "Geography",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Geography-P1-Nov-2020-Afr-2.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Geography-P1-Nov-2020-Memo-Afr-2.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 465,
                        "subject": "Geography",
                        "title": "Paper 1 Annexure",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Geography-P1-Nov-2020-Annexure-Afr-2.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 466,
                        "subject": "Geography",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Geography-P2-Nov-2020-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Geography-P1-Nov-2020-Memo-Afr-2-1.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 467,
                        "subject": "History",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/History-P1-Nov-2020-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/History-P1-Nov-2020-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 468,
                        "subject": "History",
                        "title": "Paper 1 Addendum",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/History-P1-Nov-2020-Addendum-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 469,
                        "subject": "History",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/History-P2-Nov-2020-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/History-P2-Nov-2020-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 470,
                        "subject": "History",
                        "title": "Paper 2 Addendum",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/History-P2-Nov-2020-Addendum-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 471,
                        "subject": "Hospitality Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Hospitality-Studies-Nov-2020-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Hospitality-Studies-Nov-2020-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 472,
                        "subject": "Information Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Information-Technology-P1-Nov-2020-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Information-Technology-P1-Nov-2020-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 473,
                        "subject": "Information Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Information-Technology-P2-Nov-2020-Afr-1.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Information-Technology-P2-Nov-2020-Memo-Afr-1.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 474,
                        "subject": "Life Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Life-Sciences-P1-Nov-2020-Afr-2.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Life-Sciences-P1-Nov-2020-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 475,
                        "subject": "Life Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Life-Sciences-P2-Nov-2020-Afr-2.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Life-Sciences-P2-Nov-2020-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 476,
                        "subject": "Mathematical Literacy",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematical-Literacy-P1-Nov-2020-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematical-Literacy-P1-Nov-2020-Memo-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 477,
                        "subject": "Mathematical Literacy",
                        "title": "Paper 1 Addendum",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematical-Literacy-P1-Nov-2020-Addendum-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 478,
                        "subject": "Mathematical Literacy",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematical-Literacy-P2-Nov-2020-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematical-Literacy-P2-Nov-2020-Memo-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 479,
                        "subject": "Mathematical Literacy",
                        "title": "Paper 2 Addendum",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematical-Literacy-P2-Nov-2020-Addendum-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 480,
                        "subject": "Mathematics",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematics-P2-Nov-2020-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematics-P2-Nov-2020-Memo-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 481,
                        "subject": "Mathematics",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematics-P1-Nov-2020-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematics-P1-Nov-2020-Memo-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 482,
                        "subject": "Mechanical Technology",
                        "title": "Welding and Metalwork Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mechanical-Technology-Nov-2020-Welding-Metalwork-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mechanical-Technology-Nov-2020-Welding-and-Metalwork-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 483,
                        "subject": "Mechanical Technology",
                        "title": "Fitting and Machining Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mechanical-Technology-Nov-2020-Fitting-Machining-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mechanical-Technology-Nov-2020-Fitting-Machining-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 484,
                        "subject": "Mechanical Technology",
                        "title": "Automative Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mechanical-Technology-Nov-2020-Automotive-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mechanical-Technology-Nov-2020-Automotive-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 485,
                        "subject": "Music",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Music-P2-Nov-2020-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Music-P2-Nov-2020-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 486,
                        "subject": "Music",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Music-P1-Nov-2020-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Music-P1-Nov-2020-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 487,
                        "subject": "Physical Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Physical-Sciences-P2-Nov-2020-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Physical-Sciences-P2-Nov-2020-Eng-Afr-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 488,
                        "subject": "Physical Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Physical-Sciences-P1-Nov-2020-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Physical-Sciences-P1-Nov-2020-Eng-Afr-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 489,
                        "subject": "Religion Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Religion-Studies-P2-NSC-Nov-2020-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Religion-Studies-P2-NSC-Nov-2020-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 490,
                        "subject": "Religion Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Religion-Studies-P1-NSC-Nov-2020-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Religion-Studies-P1-NSC-Nov-2020-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 491,
                        "subject": "Religion Studies (Senior Certificate)",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Religion-Studies-P2-SC-Nov-2020-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Religion-Studies-P2-SC-Nov-2020-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 492,
                        "subject": "Religion Studies (Senior Certificate)",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Religion-Studies-P1-SC-Nov-2020-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Religion-Studies-P1-SC-Nov-2020-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 493,
                        "subject": "Technical Mathematics",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Mathematics-P2-Nov-2020-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Mathematics-P2-Nov-2020-Answer-Book-Eng-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 494,
                        "subject": "Technical Mathematics",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Mathematics-P1-Nov-2020-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Mathematics-P1-Nov-2020-Eng-Afr-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 495,
                        "subject": "Technical Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Sciences-P2-Nov-2020-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Sciences-P2-Nov-2020-Eng-Afr-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 496,
                        "subject": "Technical Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Sciences-P1-Nov-2020-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Sciences-P1-Nov-2020-Eng-Afr-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 497,
                        "subject": "Tourism",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tourism-Nov-2020-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tourism-Nov-2020-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 498,
                        "subject": "Visual Arts",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Visual-Arts-P2-Nov-2020-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 499,
                        "subject": "Visual Arts",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Visual-Arts-P1-Nov-2020-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Visual-Arts-P1-Nov-2020-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "english": [
                    {
                        "id": 500,
                        "subject": "Accounting",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Accounting-P1-NSC-Nov-2020-Eng-2.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Accounting-P1-Nov-2020-Memo-Eng-2.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 501,
                        "subject": "Accounting",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Accounting-P2-NSC-Nov-2020-Eng-2.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Accounting-P2-Nov-2020-Memo-Eng-2.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 502,
                        "subject": "Accounting (Senior Certificate)",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Accounting-SC-Nov-2020-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Accounting-Nov-2020-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 503,
                        "subject": "Agricultural Management Practices",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Management-Practices-Nov-2020-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Management-Practices-Nov-2020-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 504,
                        "subject": "Agricultural Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Sciences-P1-Nov-2020-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Sciences-P1-Nov-2020-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 505,
                        "subject": "Agricultural Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Sciences-P2-Nov-2020-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Sciences-P2-Nov-2020-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 506,
                        "subject": "Agricultural Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Technology-Nov-2020-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Technology-Nov-2020-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 507,
                        "subject": "Business Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Business-Studies-P1-NSC-Nov-2020-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 508,
                        "subject": "Business Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Business-Studies-P2-NSC-Nov-2020-Eng-2.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 509,
                        "subject": "Business Studies(Senior Certificate)",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Business-Studies-SC-Nov-2020-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Business-Studies-Nov-2020-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 510,
                        "subject": "Civil Technology",
                        "title": "Civil Services Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Civil-Technology-Nov-2020-Civil-Services-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Civil-Technology-Nov-2020-Civil-Services-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 511,
                        "subject": "Civil Technology",
                        "title": "Woodworking Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Civil-Technology-Nov-2020-Woodworking-Eng-1.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Civil-Technology-Nov-2020-Woodworking-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 512,
                        "subject": "Civil Technology",
                        "title": "Construction Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Civil-Technology-Nov-2020-Construction-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Civil-Technology-Nov-2020-Construction-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 513,
                        "subject": "Computer Application Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Computer-Application-Technology-P1-Nov-2020-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Computer-Application-Technology-P1-Nov-2020-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 514,
                        "subject": "Computer Application Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Computer-Application-Technology-P2-Nov-2020-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Computer-Application-Technology-P2-Nov-2020-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 515,
                        "subject": "Consumer Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Consumer-Studies-Nov-2020-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Consumer-Studies-Nov-2020-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 516,
                        "subject": "Dance Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Dance-Studies-Nov-2020-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Dance-Studies-Nov-2020-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 517,
                        "subject": "Design",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Design-P1-Nov-2020-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Design-P1-Nov-2020-Memo-Eng-1.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 518,
                        "subject": "Design",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Design-P2-Nov-2020-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 519,
                        "subject": "Dramatic Arts",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Dramatic-Arts-Nov-2020-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Dramatic-Arts-Nov-2020-Eng-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 520,
                        "subject": "Economics",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Economics-P1-Nov-2020-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Economics-P1-Nov-2020-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 521,
                        "subject": "Economics",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Economics-P2-Nov-2020-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Economics-P2-Nov-2020-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 522,
                        "subject": "Electrical Technology",
                        "title": "Digitals Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Electrical-Technology-Nov-2020-Digital-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Electrical-Technology-Nov-2020-Digital-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 523,
                        "subject": "Electrical Technology",
                        "title": "Electronic Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Electrical-Technology-Nov-2020-Electronics-Eng-1.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Electrical-Technology-Nov-2020-Electronics-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 524,
                        "subject": "Electrical Technology",
                        "title": "Power Systems Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Electrical-Technology-Nov-2020-Power-Systems-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Electrical-Technology-Nov-2020-Power-Systems-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 525,
                        "subject": "Engineering Graphic and Design",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Engineering-Graphics-Design-P1-Nov-2020-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/EGD-P1-Nov-2020-Eng-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 526,
                        "subject": "Engineering Graphic and Design",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/EGD-P2-Nov-2020-Eng-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 527,
                        "subject": "Geography",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Geography-P1-Nov-2020-Eng-2.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Geography-P1-Nov-2020-Memo-Eng-2.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 528,
                        "subject": "Geography",
                        "title": "Paper 1 Annexure",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Geography-P1-Nov-2020-Annexure-Eng-2.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 529,
                        "subject": "Geography",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Geography-P2-Nov-2020-Eng-1.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Geography-P2-Nov-2020-Memo-Eng-2.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 530,
                        "subject": "History",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/History-P1-Nov-2020-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/History-P1-Nov-2020-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 531,
                        "subject": "History",
                        "title": "Paper 1 Addendum",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/History-P1-Nov-2020-Addendum-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 532,
                        "subject": "History",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/History-P2-Nov-2020-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/History-P2-Nov-2020-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 533,
                        "subject": "History",
                        "title": "Paper 2 Addendum",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/History-P2-Nov-2020-Addendum-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 534,
                        "subject": "Hospitality Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Hospitality-Studies-Nov-2020-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Hospitality-Studies-Nov-2020-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 535,
                        "subject": "Information Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Information-Technology-P1-Nov-2020-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Information-Technology-P1-Nov-2020-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 536,
                        "subject": "Information Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Information-Technology-P2-Nov-2020-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Information-Technology-P2-Nov-2020-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 537,
                        "subject": "Life Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Life-Sciences-P1-Nov-2020-Eng-2.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Life-Sciences-P1-Nov-2020-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 538,
                        "subject": "Life Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Life-Sciences-P2-Nov-2020-Eng-2.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Life-Sciences-P2-Nov-2020-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 539,
                        "subject": "Mathematical Literacy",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematical-Literacy-P1-Nov-2020-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematical-Literacy-P1-Nov-2020-Memo-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 540,
                        "subject": "Mathematical Literacy",
                        "title": "Paper 1 Addendum",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematical-Literacy-P1-Nov-2020-Addendum-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 541,
                        "subject": "Mathematical Literacy",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematical-Literacy-P2-Nov-2020-Eng-1.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematical-Literacy-P2-Nov-2020-Memo-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 542,
                        "subject": "Mathematical Literacy",
                        "title": "Paper 2 Addendum",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematical-Literacy-P2-Nov-2020-Addendum-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 543,
                        "subject": "Mathematics",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematics-P2-Nov-2020-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematics-P2-Nov-2020-Memo-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 544,
                        "subject": "Mathematics",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematics-P1-Nov-2020-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mathematics-P1-Nov-2020-Memo-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 545,
                        "subject": "Mechanical Technology",
                        "title": "Welding and Metalwork Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mechanical-Technology-Nov-2020-Welding-Metalwork-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mechanical-Technology-Nov-2020-Welding-Metalwork-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 546,
                        "subject": "Mechanical Technology",
                        "title": "Fitting and Machining Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mechanical-Technology-Nov-2020-Fitting-Machining-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mechanical-Technology-Nov-2020-Fitting-Machining-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 547,
                        "subject": "Mechanical Technology",
                        "title": "Automative Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mechanical-Technology-Nov-2020-Automotive-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Mechanical-Technology-Nov-2020-Automotive-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 548,
                        "subject": "Music",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Music-P2-Nov-2020-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Music-P2-Nov-2020-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 549,
                        "subject": "Music",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Music-P1-Nov-2020-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Music-P1-Nov-2020-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 550,
                        "subject": "Physical Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Physical-Sciences-P2-Nov-2020-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Physical-Sciences-P2-Nov-2020-Eng-Afr-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 551,
                        "subject": "Physical Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Physical-Sciences-P1-Nov-2020-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Physical-Sciences-P1-Nov-2020-Eng-Afr-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 552,
                        "subject": "Religion Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Religion-Studies-P2-NSC-Nov-2020-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Religion-Studies-P2-NSC-Nov-2020-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 553,
                        "subject": "Religion Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Religion-Studies-P1-NSC-Nov-2020-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Religion-Studies-P1-NSC-Nov-2020-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 554,
                        "subject": "Religion Studies (Senior Certificate)",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Religion-Studies-P2-SC-Nov-2020-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Religion-Studies-P2-SC-Nov-2020-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 555,
                        "subject": "Religion Studies (Senior Certificate)",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Religion-Studies-P1-SC-Nov-2020-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Religion-Studies-P1-SC-Nov-2020-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 556,
                        "subject": "Technical Mathematics",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Mathematics-P2-Nov-2020-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Mathematics-P2-Nov-2020-Answer-Book-Eng-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 557,
                        "subject": "Technical Mathematics",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Mathematics-P1-Nov-2020-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Mathematics-P1-Nov-2020-Eng-Afr-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 558,
                        "subject": "Technical Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Sciences-P2-Nov-2020-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Sciences-P2-Nov-2020-Eng-Afr-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 559,
                        "subject": "Technical Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Sciences-P1-Nov-2020-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Technical-Sciences-P1-Nov-2020-Eng-Afr-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 560,
                        "subject": "Tourism",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tourism-Nov-2020-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tourism-Nov-2020-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 561,
                        "subject": "Visual Arts",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Visual-Arts-P2-Nov-2020-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 562,
                        "subject": "Visual Arts",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Visual-Arts-P1-Nov-2020-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Visual-Arts-P1-Nov-2020-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ]
            }
        }
    },
    "2019": {
        "november": {
            "language": {
                "afrikaans": [
                    {
                        "id": 563,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Afrikaans-FAL-P1-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Afrikaans-FAL-P1-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 564,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Afrikaans-FAL-P2-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Afrikaans-FAL-P2-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 565,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Afrikaans-FAL-P3-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Afrikaans-FAL-P3-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 566,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans Home Language 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Afrikaans-HL-P1-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Afrikaans-HL-P1-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 567,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans Home Language 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Afrikaans-HL-P2-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Afrikaans-HL-P2-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 568,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans Home Language 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Afrikaans-HL-P3-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Afrikaans-HL-P3-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 569,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans Second Additional Language P1(Vrystaat)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-Nov-2019-Vrystaat.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-Nov-2019-Memo-Vrystaat.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 570,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans Second Additional Language P1(Gauteng)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-Nov-2019-Gauteng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-Nov-2019-Memo-Gauteng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 571,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans Second Additional Language P1(Kwazulu-Natal)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-Nov-2019-KwaZulu-Natal.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-Nov-2019-Memo-KwaZulu-Natal.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 572,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans Second Additional Language P1(Limpopo)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-Nov-2019-Limpopo.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-Nov-2019-Memo-Limpopo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 573,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans Second Additional Language P1(Mpumalanga)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-Nov-2019-Mpumalanga.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-Nov-2019-Memo-Mpumalanga.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 574,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans Second Additional Language P1(Noordwes)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-Nov-2019-Noordwes.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-Nov-2019-Memo-Noordwes.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 575,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans Second Additional Language P1(Noord-kaap)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-Nov-2019-Noord-Kaap.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-Nov-2019-Memo-Noord-Kaap.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 576,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans Second Additional Language P1(Wes-Kaap)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-Nov-2019-Wes-Kaap.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-Nov-2019-Memo-Wes-Kaap.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 577,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans Second Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Afrikaans-SAL-P2-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Afrikaans-SAL-P2-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "english": [
                    {
                        "id": 578,
                        "subject": "english",
                        "title": "English First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/English-FAL-P1-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/English-FAL-P1-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 579,
                        "subject": "english",
                        "title": "English First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/English-FAL-P2-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/English-FAL-P2-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 580,
                        "subject": "english",
                        "title": "English First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/English-FAL-P3-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/English-FAL-P3-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 581,
                        "subject": "english",
                        "title": "English Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/English-HL-P1-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/English-HL-P1-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 582,
                        "subject": "english",
                        "title": "English Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/English-HL-P2-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/English-HL-P2-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 583,
                        "subject": "english",
                        "title": "English Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/English-HL-P3-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/English-HL-P3-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 584,
                        "subject": "english",
                        "title": "English Second Additional Language P1(Gauteng)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/English-SAL-P1-Nov-2019-Gauteng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/English-SAL-P1-Nov-2019-Memo-Gauteng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 585,
                        "subject": "english",
                        "title": "English Second Additional Language P1(Western Cape)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/English-SAL-P1-Nov-2019-Western-Cape.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/English-SAL-P1-Nov-2019-Memo-Western-Cape.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 586,
                        "subject": "english",
                        "title": "English Second Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/English-SAL-P2-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/English-SAL-P2-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "isindebele": [
                    {
                        "id": 587,
                        "subject": "isindebele",
                        "title": "IsiNdebele First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiNdebele-FAL-P1-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiNdebele-FAL-P1-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 588,
                        "subject": "isindebele",
                        "title": "IsiNdebele First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiNdebele-FAL-P2-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiNdebele-FAL-P2-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 589,
                        "subject": "isindebele",
                        "title": "IsiNdebele First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiNdebele-FAL-P3-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiNdebele-FAL-P3-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 590,
                        "subject": "isindebele",
                        "title": "IsiNdebele Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiNdebele-HL-P1-Nov-2019.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 591,
                        "subject": "isindebele",
                        "title": "IsiNdebele Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiNdebele-HL-P2-Nov-2019.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 592,
                        "subject": "isindebele",
                        "title": "IsiNdebele Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiNdebele-HL-P3-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiNdebele-HL-P3-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 593,
                        "subject": "isindebele",
                        "title": "IsiNdebele Second Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiNdebele-SAL-P1-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiNdebele-SAL-P1-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 594,
                        "subject": "isindebele",
                        "title": "IsiNdebele Second Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiNdebele-SAL-P2-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiNdebele-SAL-P2-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "isixhosa": [
                    {
                        "id": 595,
                        "subject": "isixhosa",
                        "title": "Isixhosa First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiXhosa-FAL-P1-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiXhosa-FAL-P1-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 596,
                        "subject": "isixhosa",
                        "title": "Isixhosa First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiXhosa-FAL-P2-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiXhosa-FAL-P2-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 597,
                        "subject": "isixhosa",
                        "title": "Isixhosa First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiXhosa-FAL-P3-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiXhosa-FAL-P3-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 598,
                        "subject": "isixhosa",
                        "title": "Isixhosa Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiXhosa-HL-P1-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiXhosa-HL-P1-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 599,
                        "subject": "isixhosa",
                        "title": "Isixhosa Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiXhosa-HL-P2-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiXhosa-HL-P2-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 600,
                        "subject": "isixhosa",
                        "title": "Isixhosa Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiXhosa-HL-P3-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiXhosa-HL-P3-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 601,
                        "subject": "isixhosa",
                        "title": "Isixhosa Second Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiXhosa-SAL-P1-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiXhosa-SAL-P1-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 602,
                        "subject": "isixhosa",
                        "title": "Isixhosa Second Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiXhosa-SAL-P2-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiXhosa-SAL-P2-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "isizulu": [
                    {
                        "id": 603,
                        "subject": "isizulu",
                        "title": "IsiZulu First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiZulu-FAL-P1-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiZulu-FAL-P1-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 604,
                        "subject": "isizulu",
                        "title": "IsiZulu First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiZulu-FAL-P2-Nov-2019-1.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiZulu-FAL-P2-Nov-2019-Memo-1.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 605,
                        "subject": "isizulu",
                        "title": "IsiZulu First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiZulu-FAL-P3-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiZulu-HL-P3-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 606,
                        "subject": "isizulu",
                        "title": "IsiZulu Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiZulu-HL-P1-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiZulu-HL-P1-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 607,
                        "subject": "isizulu",
                        "title": "IsiZulu Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiZulu-HL-P2-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiZulu-HL-P2-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 608,
                        "subject": "isizulu",
                        "title": "IsiZulu Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiZulu-HL-P3-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiZulu-HL-P3-Nov-2019-Memo-1.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 609,
                        "subject": "isizulu",
                        "title": "IsiZulu Second Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiZulu-SAL-P1-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiZulu-SAL-P1-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 610,
                        "subject": "isizulu",
                        "title": "IsiZulu Second Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiZulu-SAL-P2-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/IsiZulu-SAL-P2-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "sepedi": [
                    {
                        "id": 611,
                        "subject": "sepedi",
                        "title": "Sepedi Second Additional Language P1 (Limpopo)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Sepedi-SAL-P1-Nov-2019-Limpopo.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Sepedi-SAL-P1-Nov-2019-Memo-Limpopo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 612,
                        "subject": "sepedi",
                        "title": "Sepedi Second Additional Language P1 (Gauteng)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Sepedi-SAL-P1-Nov-2019-Gauteng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Sepedi-SAL-P1-Nov-2019-Memo-Gauteng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 613,
                        "subject": "sepedi",
                        "title": "Sepedi First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Sepedi-FAL-P1-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Sepedi-FAL-P1-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 614,
                        "subject": "sepedi",
                        "title": "Sepedi First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Sepedi-FAL-P2-Nov-2019-1.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 615,
                        "subject": "sepedi",
                        "title": "Sepedi First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Sepedi-FAL-P3-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Sepedi-FAL-P3-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 616,
                        "subject": "sepedi",
                        "title": "Sepedi Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Sepedi-HL-P1-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Sepedi-HL-P1-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 617,
                        "subject": "sepedi",
                        "title": "Sepedi Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Sepedi-HL-P2-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Sepedi-HL-P2-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 618,
                        "subject": "sepedi",
                        "title": "Sepedi Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Sepedi-HL-P3-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Sepedi-HL-P3-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 619,
                        "subject": "sepedi",
                        "title": "Sepedi Second Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Sepedi-SAL-P2-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Sepedi-SAL-P2-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "sesotho": [
                    {
                        "id": 620,
                        "subject": "sesotho",
                        "title": "Sesotho Second Additional Language P1 (Gauteng)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Sesotho-SAL-P1-Nov-2019-Gauteng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Sesotho-SAL-P1-Nov-2019-Memo-Gauteng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 621,
                        "subject": "sesotho",
                        "title": "Sesotho Second Additional Language P1 (Free state)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Sesotho-SAL-P1-Nov-2019-Free-State.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Sesotho-SAL-P1-Nov-2019-Memo-Free-State.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 622,
                        "subject": "sesotho",
                        "title": "Sesotho First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Sesotho-HL-P1-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Sesotho-FAL-P1-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 623,
                        "subject": "sesotho",
                        "title": "Sesotho First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Sesotho-FAL-P2-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Sesotho-FAL-P2-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 624,
                        "subject": "sesotho",
                        "title": "Sesotho First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Sesotho-FAL-P3-Nov-2019.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 625,
                        "subject": "sesotho",
                        "title": "Sesotho Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Sesotho-HL-P1-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Sesotho-HL-P1-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 626,
                        "subject": "sesotho",
                        "title": "Sesotho Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Sesotho-HL-P2-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Sesotho-HL-P2-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 627,
                        "subject": "sesotho",
                        "title": "Sesotho Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Sesotho-HL-P3-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Sepedi-HL-P3-Nov-2019-Memo-1.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 628,
                        "subject": "sesotho",
                        "title": "Sesotho Second Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Sesotho-SAL-P2-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Sesotho-SAL-P2-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "setswana": [
                    {
                        "id": 629,
                        "subject": "setswana",
                        "title": "Setswana First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Setswana-FAL-P1-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Setswana-FAL-P1-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 630,
                        "subject": "setswana",
                        "title": "Setswana First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Setswana-FAL-P2-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Setswana-FAL-P2-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 631,
                        "subject": "setswana",
                        "title": "Setswana First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Setswana-FAL-P3-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Setswana-FAL-P3-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 632,
                        "subject": "setswana",
                        "title": "Setswana Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Setswana-HL-P1-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Setswana-HL-P1-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 633,
                        "subject": "setswana",
                        "title": "Setswana Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Setswana-HL-P2-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Setswana-HL-P2-Nov-2019-Memp.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 634,
                        "subject": "setswana",
                        "title": "Setswana Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Setswana-HL-P3-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Setswana-HL-P3-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 635,
                        "subject": "setswana",
                        "title": "Setswana Second Additional Language P1(Gauteng)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Setswana-SAL-P1-Nov-2019-Gauteng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Setswana-SAL-P1-Nov-2019-Gauteng-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 636,
                        "subject": "setswana",
                        "title": "Setswana Second Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Setswana-SAL-P2-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Setswana-SAL-P2-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "siswati": [
                    {
                        "id": 637,
                        "subject": "siswati",
                        "title": "Siswati First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Siswati-FAL-P1-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Siswati-FAL-P1-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 638,
                        "subject": "siswati",
                        "title": "Siswati First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Siswati-FAL-P2-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Siswati-FAL-P2-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 639,
                        "subject": "siswati",
                        "title": "Siswati First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Siswati-FAL-P3-Nov-2019.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 640,
                        "subject": "siswati",
                        "title": "Siswati Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Siswati-HL-P1-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Siswati-HL-P1-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 641,
                        "subject": "siswati",
                        "title": "Siswati Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Siswati-HL-P2-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Siswati-HL-P2-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 642,
                        "subject": "siswati",
                        "title": "Siswati Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Siswati-HL-P3-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Siswati-HL-P3-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "tshivenda": [
                    {
                        "id": 643,
                        "subject": "tshivenda",
                        "title": "Tshivenda First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Tshivenda-FAL-P1-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Tshivenda-FAL-P1-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 644,
                        "subject": "tshivenda",
                        "title": "Tshivenda First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Tshivenda-FAL-P2-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Tshivenda-FAL-P2-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 645,
                        "subject": "tshivenda",
                        "title": "Tshivenda First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Tshivenda-FAL-P3-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Tshivenda-FAL-P3-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 646,
                        "subject": "tshivenda",
                        "title": "Tshivenda Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Tshivenda-HL-P1-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Tshivenda-HL-P1-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 647,
                        "subject": "tshivenda",
                        "title": "Tshivenda Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Tshivenda-HL-P2-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Tshivenda-HL-P2-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 648,
                        "subject": "tshivenda",
                        "title": "Tshivenda Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Tshivenda-HL-P3-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Tshivenda-HL-P3-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "xitsonga": [
                    {
                        "id": 649,
                        "subject": "xitsonga",
                        "title": "Xitsonga First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Xitsonga-FAL-P1-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Xitsonga-FAL-P1-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 650,
                        "subject": "Xitsonga",
                        "title": "Xitsonga First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Xitsonga-FAL-P2-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Xitsonga-FAL-P2-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 651,
                        "subject": "Xitsonga",
                        "title": "Xitsonga First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Xitsonga-FAL-P3-Nov-2019.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 652,
                        "subject": "Xitsonga",
                        "title": "Xitsonga Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Xitsonga-HL-P1-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Xitsonga-HL-P1-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 653,
                        "subject": "Xitsonga",
                        "title": "Xitsonga Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Xitsonga-HL-P2-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Xitsonga-HL-P2-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 654,
                        "subject": "Xitsonga",
                        "title": "Xitsonga Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Xitsonga-HL-P3-Nov-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Xitsonga-HL-P3-Nov-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "sign-language": [
                    {
                        "id": 655,
                        "subject": "South African Sign Language(Final)",
                        "title": "SASL Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {}
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 656,
                        "subject": "South African Sign Language(Final)",
                        "title": "SASL Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {}
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 657,
                        "subject": "South African Sign Language(Final)",
                        "title": "SASL Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {}
                    }
                ]
            },
            "non-language": {
                "afrikaans": [
                    {
                        "id": 658,
                        "subject": "Accounting",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Accounting-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Accounting-Nov-2019-Nov-2019-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 659,
                        "subject": "Agricultural Management Practices",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Agricultural-Management-Practices-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Agricultural-Management-Practices-Nov-2019-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 660,
                        "subject": "Agricultural Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Agricultural-Sciences-P1-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Agricultural-Sciences-P1-Nov-2019-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 661,
                        "subject": "Agricultural Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Agricultural-Sciences-P2-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Agricultural-Sciences-P2-Nov-2019-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 662,
                        "subject": "Agricultural Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Agricultural-Technology-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 663,
                        "subject": "Business Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Business-Studies-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 664,
                        "subject": "Civil Technology",
                        "title": "Woodworking Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Civil-Technology-Nov-2019-Woodworking-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 665,
                        "subject": "Civil Technology",
                        "title": "Civil Services Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Civil-Technology-Nov-2019-Civil-Services-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 666,
                        "subject": "Civil Technology",
                        "title": "Construction Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Civil-Technology-Nov-2019-Construction-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 667,
                        "subject": "Computer Application Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Computer-Application-Technology-P1-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 668,
                        "subject": "Computer Application Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Computer-Application-Technology-P2-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 669,
                        "subject": "Consumer Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Consumer-Studies-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 670,
                        "subject": "Dance studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Dance-Studies-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 671,
                        "subject": "Design",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Design-P1-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 672,
                        "subject": "Design",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Design-P2-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 673,
                        "subject": "Dramatic Arts",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Dramatic-Arts-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 674,
                        "subject": "Economics",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Economics-P1-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 675,
                        "subject": "Economics",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Economics-P2-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 676,
                        "subject": "Electrical Technology",
                        "title": "Digitals Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Electrical-Technology-Nov-2019-Digital-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 677,
                        "subject": "Electrical Technology",
                        "title": "Electronics Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Electrical-Technology-Nov-2019-Electronics-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 678,
                        "subject": "Electrical Technology",
                        "title": "Power Systems Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Electrical-Technology-Nov-2019-Power-System-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 679,
                        "subject": "Engineering Graphic and Design",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Engineering-Graphics-Design-P1-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 680,
                        "subject": "Engineering Graphic and Design",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Engineering-Graphics-Design-P2-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 681,
                        "subject": "Geography",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Geography-P1-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 682,
                        "subject": "Geography",
                        "title": "Annexure Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Geography-P1-Nov-2019-Annexure-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 683,
                        "subject": "Geography",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Geography-P2-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 684,
                        "subject": "History",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/History-P1-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 685,
                        "subject": "History",
                        "title": "Paper 1 Addendum",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/History-P1-Nov-2019-Addendum-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 686,
                        "subject": "History",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/History-P2-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 687,
                        "subject": "History",
                        "title": "Paper 2 Addendum",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/History-P2-Nov-2019-Addendum-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 688,
                        "subject": "Hospitality Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Hospitality-Studies-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 689,
                        "subject": "Information Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Information-Technology-P1-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 690,
                        "subject": "Information Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Information-Technology-P2-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 691,
                        "subject": "Life Orientation",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Life-Orientation-September-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 692,
                        "subject": "Life Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Life-Sciences-P1-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 693,
                        "subject": "Life Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Life-Sciences-P2-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 694,
                        "subject": "Mathematical Literacy",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mathematical-Literacy-P1-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 695,
                        "subject": "Mathematical Literacy",
                        "title": "Paper 1 Addendum",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mathematical-Literacy-P1-Nov-2019-Addendum-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 696,
                        "subject": "Mathematical Literacy",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mathematical-Literacy-P2-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 697,
                        "subject": "Mathematical Literacy",
                        "title": "Paper 2 Addendum",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mathematical-Literacy-P2-Nov-2019-Addendum-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 698,
                        "subject": "Mathematics",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mathematics-P2-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 699,
                        "subject": "Mathematics",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mathematics-P1-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 700,
                        "subject": "Mechanical Technology",
                        "title": "Welding and Metalwork Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mechanical-Technology-Nov-2019-Welding-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 701,
                        "subject": "Mechanical Technology",
                        "title": "Fitting and Machining Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mechanical-Technology-Nov-2019-Fitting-Machining-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 702,
                        "subject": "Mechanical Technology",
                        "title": "Automative Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mechanical-Technology-Nov-2019-Automotive-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 703,
                        "subject": "Music",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Music-P2-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 704,
                        "subject": "Music",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Music-P1-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 705,
                        "subject": "Physical Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Physical-Sciences-P2-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 706,
                        "subject": "Physical Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Physical-Sciences-P1-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 707,
                        "subject": "Religion Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Religion-Studies-P2-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 708,
                        "subject": "Religion Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Religion-Studies-P1-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 709,
                        "subject": "Technical Mathematics",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Technical-Mathematics-P2-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 710,
                        "subject": "Technical Mathematics",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Technical-Mathematics-P1-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 711,
                        "subject": "Technical Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Technical-Sciences-P2-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 712,
                        "subject": "Technical Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Technical-Sciences-P1-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 713,
                        "subject": "Tourism",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Tourism-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 714,
                        "subject": "Visual Arts",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Visual-Arts-P2-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 715,
                        "subject": "Visual Arts",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Visual-Arts-P1-Nov-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "english": [
                    {
                        "id": 716,
                        "subject": "Accounting",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Accounting-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Accounting-Nov-2019-Nov-2019-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 717,
                        "subject": "Agricultural Management Practices",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Agricultural-Management-Practices-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Agricultural-Management-Practices-Nov-2019-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 718,
                        "subject": "Agricultural Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Agricultural-Sciences-P1-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Agricultural-Sciences-P1-Nov-2019-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 719,
                        "subject": "Agricultural Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Agricultural-Sciences-P2-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Agricultural-Sciences-P2-Nov-2019-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 720,
                        "subject": "Agricultural Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Agricultural-Technology-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 721,
                        "subject": "Business Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Business-Studies-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 722,
                        "subject": "Civil Technology",
                        "title": "Civil Services Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Civil-Technology-Nov-2019-Civil-Services-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 723,
                        "subject": "Civil Technology",
                        "title": "Construction Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Civil-Technology-Nov-2019-Construction-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 724,
                        "subject": "Civil Technology",
                        "title": "Woodworking Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Civil-Technology-Nov-2019-Woodworking-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 725,
                        "subject": "Computer Application Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Computer-Application-Technology-P1-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 726,
                        "subject": "Computer Application Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Computer-Application-Technology-P2-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 727,
                        "subject": "Consumer Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Consumer-Studies-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 728,
                        "subject": "Dance studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Dance-Studies-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 729,
                        "subject": "Design",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Design-P1-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 730,
                        "subject": "Design",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Design-P2-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 731,
                        "subject": "Dramatic Arts",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Dramatic-Arts-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 732,
                        "subject": "Economics",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Economics-P1-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 733,
                        "subject": "Economics",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Economics-P2-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 734,
                        "subject": "Electrical Technology",
                        "title": "Digitals Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Electrical-Technology-Nov-2019-Digital-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 735,
                        "subject": "Electrical Technology",
                        "title": "Electronics Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Electrical-Technology-Nov-2019-Electronics-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 736,
                        "subject": "Electrical Technology",
                        "title": "Power Systems Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Electrical-Technology-Nov-2019-Power-System-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 737,
                        "subject": "Engineering Graphic and Design",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Engineering-Graphics-Design-P1-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 738,
                        "subject": "Engineering Graphic and Design",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Engineering-Graphics-Design-P2-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 739,
                        "subject": "Geography",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Geography-P1-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 740,
                        "subject": "Geography",
                        "title": "Annexure Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Geography-P1-Nov-2019-Annexure-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 741,
                        "subject": "Geography",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Geography-P2-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 742,
                        "subject": "History",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/History-P1-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 743,
                        "subject": "History",
                        "title": "Paper 1 Addendum",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/History-P1-Nov-2019-Addendum-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 744,
                        "subject": "History",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/History-P2-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 745,
                        "subject": "History",
                        "title": "Paper 2 Addendum",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/History-P2-Nov-2019-Addendum-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 746,
                        "subject": "Hospitality Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Hospitality-Studies-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 747,
                        "subject": "Information Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Information-Technology-P1-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 748,
                        "subject": "Information Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Information-Technology-P2-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 749,
                        "subject": "Life Orientation",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Life-Orientation-September-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 750,
                        "subject": "Life Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Life-Sciences-P1-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 751,
                        "subject": "Life Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Life-Sciences-P2-Nov-2019-Eng-1.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 752,
                        "subject": "Mathematical Literacy",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mathematical-Literacy-P1-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 753,
                        "subject": "Mathematical Literacy",
                        "title": "Paper 1 Addendum",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mathematical-Literacy-P1-Nov-2019-Addendum-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 754,
                        "subject": "Mathematical Literacy",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mathematical-Literacy-P2-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 755,
                        "subject": "Mathematical Literacy",
                        "title": "Paper 2 Addendum",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mathematical-Literacy-P2-Nov-2019-Addendum-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 756,
                        "subject": "Mathematics",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mathematics-P2-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 757,
                        "subject": "Mathematics",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mathematics-P1-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 758,
                        "subject": "Mechanical Technology",
                        "title": "Welding and Metalwork Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mechanical-Technology-Nov-2019-Welding-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 759,
                        "subject": "Mechanical Technology",
                        "title": "Fitting and Machining Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mechanical-Technology-Nov-2019-Fitting-Machining-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 760,
                        "subject": "Mechanical Technology",
                        "title": "Automative Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mechanical-Technology-Nov-2019-Automotive-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 761,
                        "subject": "Music",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Music-P2-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 762,
                        "subject": "Music",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Music-P1-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 763,
                        "subject": "Physical Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Physical-Sciences-P2-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 764,
                        "subject": "Physical Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Physical-Sciences-P1-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 765,
                        "subject": "Religion Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Religion-Studies-P2-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 766,
                        "subject": "Religion Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Religion-Studies-P1-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 767,
                        "subject": "Technical Mathematics",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Technical-Mathematics-P2-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 768,
                        "subject": "Technical Mathematics",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Technical-Mathematics-P1-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 769,
                        "subject": "Technical Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Technical-Sciences-P2-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 770,
                        "subject": "Technical Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Technical-Sciences-P1-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 771,
                        "subject": "Tourism",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Tourism-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 772,
                        "subject": "Visual Arts",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Visual-Arts-P2-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 773,
                        "subject": "Visual Arts",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Visual-Arts-P1-Nov-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ]
            }
        },
        "may-june": {
            "language": {
                "afrikaans": [
                    {
                        "id": 774,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-FAL-P1-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-FAL-P1-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 775,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-FAL-P2-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-FAL-P2-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 776,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "papers": {
                            "title": "Afrikaans First Additional Language Paper 3",
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-FAL-P3-May-June-2019.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 777,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans Home Language 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-HL-P1-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-HL-P1-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 778,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans Home Language 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-HL-P2-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-HL-P2-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 779,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans Home Language 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-HL-P3-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-HL-P3-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 780,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans Second Additional Language P1(Free State)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-May-June-2019-Free-State.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-May-June-2019-Memo-Free-State.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 781,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans Second Additional Language P1(Gauteng)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-May-June-2019-Gauteng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-May-June-2019-Memo-Gauteng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 782,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans Second Additional Language P1(Kwazulu-Natal)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-May-June-2019-KwaZulu-Natal.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-May-June-2019-Memo-KwaZulu-Natal.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 783,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans Second Additional Language P1(Limpopo)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-May-June-2019-Limpopo.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-May-June-2019-Memo-Limpopo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 784,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans Second Additional Language P1(Mpumalanga)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-May-June-2019-Mpumalanga.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-May-June-2019-Memo-Mpumalanga.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 785,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans Second Additional Language P1(North West)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-May-June-2019-North-West.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-May-June-2019-Memo-North-West.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 786,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans Second Additional Language P1(Northern Cape)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-May-June-2019-Northern-Cape.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-May-June-2019-Memo-Northern-Cape.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 787,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans Second Additional Language P1(Western Cape)",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-May-June-2019-Western-Cape.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P1-May-June-2019-Memo-Western-Cape.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 788,
                        "subject": "afrikaans",
                        "title": "Afrikaans Second Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P2-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-SAL-P2-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "english": [
                    {
                        "id": 789,
                        "subject": "english",
                        "title": "English First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-FAL-P1-May-June-2019-1.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-FAL-P1-May-June-2019-Memo-1.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 790,
                        "subject": "english",
                        "title": "English First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-FAL-P2-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-FAL-P2-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 791,
                        "subject": "english",
                        "title": "English First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-FAL-P3-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-FAL-P3-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 792,
                        "subject": "english",
                        "title": "English Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-HL-P1-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-HL-P1-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 793,
                        "subject": "english",
                        "title": "English Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-HL-P2-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-HL-P2-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 794,
                        "subject": "english",
                        "title": "English Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-HL-P3-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/English-HL-P3-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "isindebele": [
                    {
                        "id": 795,
                        "subject": "isindebele",
                        "title": "IsiNdebele First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiNdebele-FAL-P1-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiNdebele-FAL-P1-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 796,
                        "subject": "isindebele",
                        "title": "IsiNdebele First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiNdebele-FAL-P2-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiNdebele-FAL-P2-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 797,
                        "subject": "isindebele",
                        "title": "IsiNdebele First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiNdebele-FAL-P3-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiNdebele-FAL-P3-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 798,
                        "subject": "isindebele",
                        "title": "IsiNdebele Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiNdebele-HL-P1-May-June-2019.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 799,
                        "subject": "isindebele",
                        "title": "IsiNdebele Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiNdebele-HL-P2-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiNdebele-HL-P2-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 800,
                        "subject": "isindebele",
                        "title": "IsiNdebele Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiNdebele-HL-P3-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiNdebele-HL-P3-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "isixhosa": [
                    {
                        "id": 801,
                        "subject": "isixhosa",
                        "title": "Isixhosa First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiXhosa-FAL-P1-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiXhosa-FAL-P1-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 802,
                        "subject": "isixhosa",
                        "title": "Isixhosa First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiXhosa-FAL-P2-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiXhosa-FAL-P2-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 803,
                        "subject": "isixhosa",
                        "title": "Isixhosa First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiXhosa-FAL-P3-May-June-2019.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 804,
                        "subject": "isixhosa",
                        "title": "Isixhosa Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiNdebele-HL-P1-May-June-2019-1.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiXhosa-HL-P1-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 805,
                        "subject": "isixhosa",
                        "title": "Isixhosa Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiXhosa-HL-P2-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiXhosa-HL-P2-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 806,
                        "subject": "isixhosa",
                        "title": "Isixhosa Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiXhosa-HL-P3-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiXhosa-HL-P3-May-June-2019-Memo-1.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "isizulu": [
                    {
                        "id": 807,
                        "subject": "Isizulu",
                        "title": "IsiZulu First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiZulu-FAL-P1-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiZulu-FAL-P1-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 808,
                        "subject": "Isizulu",
                        "title": "IsiZulu First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiZulu-FAL-P2-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiZulu-FAL-P2-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 809,
                        "subject": "Isizulu",
                        "title": "IsiZulu First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiZulu-FAL-P3-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiZulu-FAL-P3-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 810,
                        "subject": "Isizulu",
                        "title": "IsiZulu Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiZulu-HL-P1-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiZulu-HL-P1-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 811,
                        "subject": "Isizulu",
                        "title": "IsiZulu Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiZulu-HL-P2-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiZulu-HL-P2-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 812,
                        "subject": "Isizulu",
                        "title": "IsiZulu Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiZulu-HL-P3-May-June-2019-1.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/IsiZulu-HL-P3-May-June-2019-Memo-1.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "sepedi": [
                    {
                        "id": 813,
                        "subject": "sepedi",
                        "title": "Sepedi First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-FAL-P1-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-FAL-P1-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 814,
                        "subject": "sepedi",
                        "title": "Sepedi First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-FAL-P2-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-FAL-P2-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 815,
                        "subject": "sepedi",
                        "title": "Sepedi First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-FAL-P3-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-FAL-P3-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 816,
                        "subject": "sepedi",
                        "title": "Sepedi Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-HL-P1-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Afrikaans-HL-P1-May-June-2019-Memo-1.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 817,
                        "subject": "sepedi",
                        "title": "Sepedi Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-HL-P2-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 818,
                        "subject": "sepedi",
                        "title": "Sepedi Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-HL-P3-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sepedi-HL-P3-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "sesotho": [
                    {
                        "id": 819,
                        "subject": "sesotho",
                        "title": "Sesotho First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sesotho-FAL-P1-May-June-2019-2.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sesotho-FAL-P1-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 820,
                        "subject": "sesotho",
                        "title": "Sesotho First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sesotho-FAL-P2-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 821,
                        "subject": "sesotho",
                        "title": "Sesotho First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sesotho-HL-P3-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sesotho-FAL-P3-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 822,
                        "subject": "sesotho",
                        "title": "Sesotho Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sesotho-HL-P3-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sesotho-FAL-P3-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 823,
                        "subject": "sesotho",
                        "title": "Sesotho Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sesotho-HL-P2-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sesotho-HL-P2-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 824,
                        "subject": "sesotho",
                        "title": "Sesotho Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sesotho-HL-P3-May-June-2019-1.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sesotho-HL-P3-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "setswana": [
                    {
                        "id": 825,
                        "subject": "setswana",
                        "title": "Setswana First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-FAL-P1-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-FAL-P1-May-June-2018-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 826,
                        "subject": "setswana",
                        "title": "Setswana First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-FAL-P2-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-FAL-P2-May-June-2018-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 827,
                        "subject": "setswana",
                        "title": "Setswana First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-FAL-P3-May-June-2018-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 828,
                        "subject": "setswana",
                        "title": "Setswana Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-HL-P1-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-HL-P1-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 829,
                        "subject": "setswana",
                        "title": "Setswana Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-HL-P2-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-HL-P2-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 830,
                        "subject": "setswana",
                        "title": "Setswana Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-HL-P3-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Setswana-HL-P3-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "siswati": [
                    {
                        "id": 831,
                        "subject": "siswati",
                        "title": "Siswati First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-FAL-P1-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-FAL-P2-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 832,
                        "subject": "siswati",
                        "title": "Siswati First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-FAL-P2-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-FAL-P2-May-June-2019-Memo-1.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 833,
                        "subject": "siswati",
                        "title": "Siswati First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-FAL-P3-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-FAL-P3-May-June-2018-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 834,
                        "subject": "siswati",
                        "title": "Siswati Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-HL-P1-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-HL-P1-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 835,
                        "subject": "siswati",
                        "title": "Siswati Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-HL-P2-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-HL-P2-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 836,
                        "subject": "siswati",
                        "title": "Siswati Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-HL-P3-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Siswati-HL-P3-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "tshivenda": [
                    {
                        "id": 837,
                        "subject": "tshivenda",
                        "title": "Tshivenda First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-FAL-P1-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-FAL-P1-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 838,
                        "subject": "tshivenda",
                        "title": "Tshivenda First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-FAL-P2-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-FAL-P2-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 839,
                        "subject": "tshivenda",
                        "title": "Tshivenda First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-FAL-P3-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-FAL-P3-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 840,
                        "subject": "tshivenda",
                        "title": "Tshivenda Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-HL-P1-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-HL-P1-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 841,
                        "subject": "tshivenda",
                        "title": "Tshivenda Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-HL-P2-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-HL-P2-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 842,
                        "subject": "tshivenda",
                        "title": "Tshivenda Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-HL-P3-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tshivenda-HL-P3-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "xitsonga": [
                    {
                        "id": 843,
                        "subject": "Xitsonga",
                        "title": "Xitsonga First Additional Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-FAL-P1-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-FAL-P1-May-June-2018-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 844,
                        "subject": "Xitsonga",
                        "title": "Xitsonga First Additional Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-FAL-P2-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-FAL-P2-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 845,
                        "subject": "Xitsonga",
                        "title": "Xitsonga First Additional Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-FAL-P3-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-FAL-P3-May-June-2018-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 846,
                        "subject": "Xitsonga",
                        "title": "Xitsonga Home Language Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-HL-P1-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-HL-P1-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 847,
                        "subject": "Xitsonga",
                        "title": "Xitsonga Home Language Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-HL-P2-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-HL-P2-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 848,
                        "subject": "Xitsonga",
                        "title": "Xitsonga Home Language Paper 3",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-HL-P3-May-June-2019.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Xitsonga-HL-P3-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ]
            },
            "non-language": {
                "afrikaans": [
                    {
                        "id": 850,
                        "subject": "Accounting",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Accounting-May-June-2019-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Accounting-May-June-2019-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 851,
                        "subject": "Agricultural Management Practices",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Management-Practices-Memo-Afr-1.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 852,
                        "subject": "Agricultural Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Sciences-P1-May-June-2019-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Sciences-P1-May-June-2019-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 853,
                        "subject": "Agricultural Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Sciences-P2-May-June-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 854,
                        "subject": "Agricultural Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {}
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 855,
                        "subject": "Business Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Business-Studies-May-June-2019-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Business-Studies-May-June-2019-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 856,
                        "subject": "Civil Technology",
                        "title": "Woodworking Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Civil-Technology-May-June-2019-Wood-Working-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Civil-Technology-May-June-2019-Wood-Working-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 857,
                        "subject": "Civil Technology",
                        "title": "Civil Services Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Civil-Technology-May-June-2019-Civil-Services-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Civil-Technology-May-June-2019-Civil-Services-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 858,
                        "subject": "Civil Technology",
                        "title": "Construction Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Civil-Technology-May-June-2019-Construction-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Civil-Technology-May-June-2019-Construction-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 859,
                        "subject": "Computer Application Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Computer-Applications-Technology-P1-May-June-2019-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Computer-Applications-Technology-P1-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 860,
                        "subject": "Computer Application Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Computer-Applications-Technology-P2-May-June-2019-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Computer-Applications-Technology-P2-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 861,
                        "subject": "Consumer Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Consumer-Studies-May-June-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 862,
                        "subject": "Dance studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Dance-Studies-May-June-2019-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Dance-Studies-May-June-2019-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 863,
                        "subject": "Design",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Design-P1-May-June-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 864,
                        "subject": "Dramatic Arts",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Dramatic-Arts-May-June-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 865,
                        "subject": "Economics",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Economics-P1-May-June-2019-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Economics-P1-May-June-2019-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 866,
                        "subject": "Economics",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Economics-P2-May-June-2019-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Economics-P2-May-June-2019-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 867,
                        "subject": "Electrical Technology",
                        "title": "Digitals Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Electrical-Technology-May-June-2019-Digital-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Electrical-Technology-May-June-2019-Digital-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 868,
                        "subject": "Electrical Technology",
                        "title": "Electronics Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Electrical-Technology-May-June-2019-Electronics-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Electrical-Technology-May-June-2019-Electronics-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 869,
                        "subject": "Electrical Technology",
                        "title": "Power Systems Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Electrical-Technology-May-June-2019-Power-System-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Electrical-Technology-May-June-2019-Power-System-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 870,
                        "subject": "Engineering Graphic and Design",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Engineering-Graphics-Design-P1-Nov-2018-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Engineering-Graphics-Design-P1-May-June-2019-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 871,
                        "subject": "Engineering Graphic and Design",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Engineering-Graphics-Design-P2-Nov-2018-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Engineering-Graphics-Design-P2-Nov-2018-FINAL-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 872,
                        "subject": "Geography",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Geography-P1-May-June-2019-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Geography-P1-May-June-2019-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 873,
                        "subject": "Geography",
                        "title": "Annexure Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Geography-P1-May-June-2019-Annexure-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 874,
                        "subject": "Geography",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Geography-P2-May-June-2019-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 875,
                        "subject": "History",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/History-P1-May-June-2019-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/History-P1-May-June-2019-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 876,
                        "subject": "History",
                        "title": "Paper 1 Addendum",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/History-P1-May-June-2019-Addendum-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 877,
                        "subject": "History",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/History-P2-May-June-2019-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/History-P2-May-June-2019-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 878,
                        "subject": "History",
                        "title": "Paper 2 Addendum",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/History-P2-Nov-2021-Addendum-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 879,
                        "subject": "Hospitality Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Hospitality-Studies-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Hospitality-Studies-Nov-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 880,
                        "subject": "Information Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Information-Technology-P1-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Information-Technology-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 881,
                        "subject": "Information Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Information-Technology-P2-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Information-Technology-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 882,
                        "subject": "Life Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Life-Sciences-P1-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Life-Sciences-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 883,
                        "subject": "Life Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Life-Sciences-P2-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Life-Sciences-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 884,
                        "subject": "Mathematical Literacy",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mathematical-Literacy-P1-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mathematical-Literacy-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 885,
                        "subject": "Mathematical Literacy",
                        "title": "Paper 1 Addendum",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mathematical-Literacy-P1-Nov-2021-Addendum-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 886,
                        "subject": "Mathematical Literacy",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mathematical-Literacy-P2-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mathematical-Literacy-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 887,
                        "subject": "Mathematical Literacy",
                        "title": "Paper 2 Addendum",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mathematical-Literacy-P2-May-June-2019-Addendum-Afr.docx"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 888,
                        "subject": "Mathematics",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mathematics-P2-May-June-2019-Afr.docx",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mathematics-P2-May-June-2019-Memo-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 889,
                        "subject": "Mathematics",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mathematics-P1-May-June-2019-Afr.docx",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mathematics-P1-May-June-2019-Memo-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 890,
                        "subject": "Mechanical Technology",
                        "title": "Welding and Metalwork Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mechanical-Technology-May-June-2019-Welding-Metalwork-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 891,
                        "subject": "Mechanical Technology",
                        "title": "Fitting and Machining Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mechanical-Technology-May-June-2019-Fitting-Machining-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mechanical-Technology-May-June-2019-Fitting-Machining-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 892,
                        "subject": "Mechanical Technology",
                        "title": "Automative Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mechanical-Technology-May-June-2019-Automotive-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mechanical-Technology-May-June-2019-Automotive-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 893,
                        "subject": "Music",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Music-P2-May-June-2019-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Music-P2-May-June-2018-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 894,
                        "subject": "Music",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Music-P1-May-June-2019-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Music-P1-May-June-2019-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 895,
                        "subject": "Physical Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Physical-Sciences-P2-May-June-2019-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Physical-Sciences-P2-May-June-2019-Memo-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 896,
                        "subject": "Physical Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Physical-Sciences-P1-May-June-2019-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Physical-Sciences-P1-May-June-2019-Memo-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 897,
                        "subject": "Religion Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Religion-Studies-P2-May-June-2019-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Religion-Studies-P2-May-June-2019-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 898,
                        "subject": "Religion Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Religion-Studies-P1-May-June-2019-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Religion-Studies-P1-May-June-2019-Memo-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 899,
                        "subject": "Technical Mathematics",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Technical-Mathematics-P2-May-June-2019-Afr.docx",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Technical-Mathematics-P2-May-June-2019-Answer-Book-Afr-Eng.docx"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 900,
                        "subject": "Technical Mathematics",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Technical-Mathematics-P1-May-June-2019-Afr.docx",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Technical-Mathematics-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 901,
                        "subject": "Technical Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Technical-Sciences-P2-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Technical-Sciences-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Eng-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 902,
                        "subject": "Technical Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Technical-Sciences-P1-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Technical-Sciences-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Eng-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 903,
                        "subject": "Tourism",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Tourism-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Tourism-Nov-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 904,
                        "subject": "Visual Arts",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Visual-Arts-P2-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 905,
                        "subject": "Visual Arts",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Visual-Arts-P1-Nov-2021-Afr.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Visual-Arts-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ],
                "english": [
                    {
                        "id": 906,
                        "subject": "Accounting",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Accounting-May-June-2019-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Accounting-May-June-2019-Memo-Eng-.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 907,
                        "subject": "Agricultural Management Practices",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Management-Practices-May-June-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 908,
                        "subject": "Agricultural Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Sciences-P1-May-June-2019-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Sciences-P1-May-June-2019-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 909,
                        "subject": "Agricultural Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Sciences-P2-May-June-2019-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Sciences-P2-May-June-2019-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 910,
                        "subject": "Agricultural Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Agricultural-Technology-May-June-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 911,
                        "subject": "Business Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Business-Studies-May-June-2019-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Business-Studies-May-June-2019-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 912,
                        "subject": "Civil Technology",
                        "title": "Civil Services Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Civil-Technology-May-June-2019-Civil-Services-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Civil-Technology-May-June-2019-Civil-Services-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 913,
                        "subject": "Civil Technology",
                        "title": "Construction Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Civil-Technology-May-June-2019-Construction-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Civil-Technology-May-June-2019-Construction-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 914,
                        "subject": "Civil Technology",
                        "title": "Woodworking Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Civil-Technology-May-June-2019-Wood-Working-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Civil-Technology-May-June-2019-Wood-Working-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 915,
                        "subject": "Computer Application Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Computer-Applications-Technology-P1-May-June-2019-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Computer-Applications-Technology-P1-May-June-2019-Memo.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 916,
                        "subject": "Computer Application Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Computer-Applications-Technology-P2-May-June-2019-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Computer-Applications-Technology-P2-May-June-2019-Memo-1.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 917,
                        "subject": "Consumer Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Consumer-Studies-May-June-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 918,
                        "subject": "Dance studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Dance-Studies-May-June-2019-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Dance-Studies-May-June-2019-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 919,
                        "subject": "Design",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Dramatic-Arts-May-June-2019-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 920,
                        "subject": "Dramatic Arts",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Dramatic-Arts-May-June-2019-Eng-1.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 921,
                        "subject": "Economics",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Economics-P1-May-June-2019-Eng-1.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Economics-P1-May-June-2019-Memo-Eng-1.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 922,
                        "subject": "Economics",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Economics-P2-May-June-2019-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Economics-P2-May-June-2019-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 923,
                        "subject": "Electrical Technology",
                        "title": "Digitals Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Electrical-Technology-May-June-2019-Digital-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Electrical-Technology-May-June-2019-Digital-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 924,
                        "subject": "Electrical Technology",
                        "title": "Electronics Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Electrical-Technology-May-June-2019-Electronics-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Electrical-Technology-May-June-2019-Electronics-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 925,
                        "subject": "Electrical Technology",
                        "title": "Power Systems Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Electrical-Technology-May-June-2019-Power-System-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Electrical-Technology-May-June-2019-Power-System-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 926,
                        "subject": "Engineering Graphic and Design",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Engineering-Graphics-Design-P1-Nov-2018-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Engineering-Graphics-Design-P1-May-June-2019-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 927,
                        "subject": "Engineering Graphic and Design",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Engineering-Graphics-Design-P2-Nov-2018-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Engineering-Graphics-Design-P2-Nov-2018-FINAL-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 928,
                        "subject": "Geography",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Geography-P1-May-June-2019-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Geography-P1-May-June-2019-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 929,
                        "subject": "Geography",
                        "title": "Annexure Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Geography-P1-May-June-2019-Annexure-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 930,
                        "subject": "Geography",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Geography-P2-May-June-2019-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Geography-P2-May-June-2019-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 931,
                        "subject": "History",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/History-P1-May-June-2019-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/History-P1-May-June-2019-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 932,
                        "subject": "History",
                        "title": "Paper 1 Addendum",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/History-P1-May-June-2019-Addendum-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 933,
                        "subject": "History",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/History-P2-May-June-2019-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/History-P2-May-June-2019-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 934,
                        "subject": "History",
                        "title": "Paper 2 Addendum",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/History-P2-Nov-2021-Addendum-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 935,
                        "subject": "Hospitality Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Hospitality-Studies-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Hospitality-Studies-Nov-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 936,
                        "subject": "Information Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Information-Technology-P1-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Information-Technology-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 937,
                        "subject": "Information Technology",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Information-Technology-P2-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Information-Technology-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 938,
                        "subject": "Life Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Life-Sciences-P1-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Life-Sciences-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 939,
                        "subject": "Life Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Life-Sciences-P2-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Life-Sciences-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 940,
                        "subject": "Mathematical Literacy",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mathematical-Literacy-P1-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mathematical-Literacy-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 941,
                        "subject": "Mathematical Literacy",
                        "title": "Paper 1 Addendum",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mathematical-Literacy-P1-Nov-2021-Addendum-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 942,
                        "subject": "Mathematical Literacy",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mathematical-Literacy-P2-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mathematical-Literacy-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 943,
                        "subject": "Mathematical Literacy",
                        "title": "Paper 2 Addendum",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mathematical-Literacy-P2-May-June-2019-Addendum-Eng.docx"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 944,
                        "subject": "Mathematics",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mathematics-P2-May-June-2019-Eng.docx",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mathematics-P2-May-June-2019-Memo-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 945,
                        "subject": "Mathematics",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mathematics-P1-May-June-2019-Eng.docx",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mathematics-P1-May-June-2019-Memo-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 946,
                        "subject": "Mechanical Technology",
                        "title": "Welding and Metalwork Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mechanical-Technology-May-June-2019-Welding-Metalwork-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mechanical-Technology-May-June-2019-Welding-Metalwork-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 947,
                        "subject": "Mechanical Technology",
                        "title": "Fitting and Machining Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mechanical-Technology-May-June-2019-Fitting-Machining-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mechanical-Technology-May-June-2019-Automotive-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 948,
                        "subject": "Mechanical Technology",
                        "title": "Automative Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mechanical-Technology-May-June-2019-Automotive-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Mechanical-Technology-May-June-2019-Automotive-Memo-Eng-1.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 949,
                        "subject": "Music",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Music-P2-May-June-2019-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Music-P1-May-June-2019-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 950,
                        "subject": "Music",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Music-P1-May-June-2019-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Music-P1-May-June-2019-Memo-Eng-1.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 951,
                        "subject": "Physical Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Physical-Sciences-P2-May-June-2019-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Physical-Sciences-P2-May-June-2019-Memo-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 952,
                        "subject": "Physical Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Physical-Sciences-P1-May-June-2019-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Physical-Sciences-P1-May-June-2019-Memo-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 953,
                        "subject": "Religion Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Religion-Studies-P2-May-June-2019-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Religion-Studies-P2-May-June-2019-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 954,
                        "subject": "Religion Studies",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Religion-Studies-P1-May-June-2019-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Religion-Studies-P1-May-June-2019-Memo-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 955,
                        "subject": "Technical Mathematics",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Technical-Mathematics-P2-May-June-2019-Eng.docx",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Technical-Mathematics-P2-May-June-2019-Answer-Book-Afr-Eng.docx"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 956,
                        "subject": "Technical Mathematics",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Technical-Mathematics-P1-May-June-2019-Eng.docx",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Technical-Mathematics-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Afr-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 957,
                        "subject": "Technical Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 2",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Technical-Sciences-P2-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Technical-Sciences-P2-Nov-2021-MG-Eng-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 958,
                        "subject": "Technical Sciences",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Technical-Sciences-P1-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Technical-Sciences-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Eng-Afr.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 959,
                        "subject": "Tourism",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Tourism-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Tourism-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 960,
                        "subject": "Visual Arts",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Visual-Arts-P2-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf"
                        },
                        "title": "Paper 2"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": 961,
                        "subject": "Visual Arts",
                        "title": "Paper 1",
                        "papers": {
                            "question": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Visual-Arts-P1-Nov-2021-Eng.pdf",
                            "answer": "https://schoolmanagement.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Visual-Arts-P1-Nov-2021-MG-Eng.pdf"
                        }
                    }
                ]
            }
        }
    }
}